They smile while they sharpen the knife
Quiet hands and knee on life
Everybody preaching peace
While they harvest weakness underneath
You thought the game was clean
You thought truth was enough
But this world don't crown the innocent
It crowns the ones who see
Usually lost control first and every time they tried to force a reaction. I became hard
I mean unless she divorces you or does something really bad to you
I mean they'll usually be forgiven right especially by me. I don't know what's wrong with me
I thought it was gay and less less susceptible to the charms and wiles of
The wicked woman right not not not women are wicked. I'm saying the particular ones right is even the particular ones they
they get away with murder and then it's like oh they're kind of like celebrated you know it's
kind of like a guy does anything it's like oh you know he needs to be murdered and uh oh and
find the woman to do it for. I'm not saying that women know how to kill I'm just saying that they
know how to clean up blood. Okay now I went too far again. I'm sorry okay well you know what I do
love I have female cats I do love I do love um gosh I worship women but it's like god how far can I
For example, we have this woman, you know, I just call her am now
But her name is laborious to say
Oh my god, I was saying a six syllable name over and over. I mean, that's a lot of labor
I'm just say am this is one syllable
you know, she
Warns me about these people don't talk to this person. I mean she did she said don't talk to them, you know
Oh, this is this person is terrible
So, and what do I mean to say?
I want her relationships repaired and stuff,
preferably while ours is maintained.
Now, I don't like to be just dumped unceremoniously.
And then, oh, well, here I am just partying
with Q and good times.
Again, my E son and my E husband,
or number one preferred sperm donor
or whatever she likes to call him.
There we are just just having a drink like nothing happened. We're talking about 80s music. We're talking about just hanging out
Oh, you know, it's not a little neck
My fucking crazy
Whoa, it's a month ago. He was a month or two months ago. He was saying the worst things about her
She's she was saying she's never been more insult in her life. She's never gonna talk to him again. Good times is a piece of shit
I mean
Musical chairs. I mean, but that's not just one example. It's just one clear example of what's going on, but
You know Christine's running around getting away with murder. I'm not literally not literally not literally
Not making an accusation. I'm just saying acting like a fool like you're saying I like a fool
My going I mean, it's like, yeah
I'll go I said I said some terrible things about her lately just in pure reaction to what she said about me
But I never went out looking for trouble like she does with me
She has to go everywhere everywhere. I go she's never been on Zayn peps
You know panel before because she I guess she thought she would be considered a pedophile or something like that
But when I if I was up there, she runs right up
Never has been on it before because you know, oh my god now that's oh, I'll go on it to harass him
Sam and I've never seen this man Sam and spend 10 cents. He's paying to kick me off of shows
I mean it gets ridiculous and then no one's talking
No, I'll fucking see who is his blog. There's only one person that should even be blocked in the chat
His name is Tony
You know
It's his last name. I don't know. It's I think it's like Tony
Tony the tiger or something like that
I heard everyone was blocked or something. I haven't checked it out yet. Let me see if everyone's blocked
I'm not even getting to the people that I don't trust right now
Let me look into my
List now. I'm gonna read all the names of the blocked people and if you vouch for the person I
Want you to say okay, so I need to I need to unmod. Oh my god Alexander was still a mod. Oh my dear god
Okay
That's fixed real quick. Okay. Hold on a second
Geez, now in the wonder of everyone,
she was fucking Alexander was a managing mod.
Can you believe it?
How slow am I?
How fucking slow am I?
How long has it been?
She's been like eight days
and she just completely turned on me again.
Again, okay, hold on a second.
Hi Rudy, okay, so let me just check this for a minute.
So let's go through the list
and you tell me if, and if nobody talks,
I'm just gonna stop having a chat.
I'm just gonna block,
I'm gonna start blocking everybody in the chat
Nobody will talk. It will just be me. Okay, so let me check out these moderators
Okay, Amber is a moderator again Patrick. Where's Leah Patrick Ricky?
spunky
2020 rose red. I wear my moderators. I mean being Patriot Chanel Apollo. I need my moderators here, okay?
Even some are still moderators
Hi babies even I'm not mad at summer even though she didn't say hello to me in several months even though
We've been in the same chat together
Okay, I mean you can at least say hi
I mean I would have said hi, but you didn't you don't shut your mouth for the entire time
You're in there to yell at poor mercy or whatever, but okay stop any you'll be unmodded
Okay
Chicken Kicks is good, Shan Camp or Race of Rain.
See, Brandon does not mod it, if he mods, he's good, okay.
So those are all the mods, okay, so I got enough mods.
Now, Joe Shippley, okay, well, now let's go through
the hidden users, guys.
And there's a few, there's quite a few.
Tell me if I should unblock them, okay?
We have Cheta Bob Slob.
We have Israeli YouTube Investigation Team.
We have Lazy Subby, we have Bimmy James, we have Oh God, Oh Man, Oh God, Oh Man, Oh God, Oh God.
We have Yellow Snowman, we have Jimmy Love's Lady Boyz, Flight, we have Day Kwan, who has a female picture.
We have Lady Bathory, who will be on Permanent Band.
I mean Uter, I kept trying to like give you another chance, but you're just so annoying
I think you're funny and their chance, but you don't be you're such a dick to me
We have Katie Crip Aiden Spam King Aiden Poppy Tender officer
Colt of psychos this Melissa
psyche haters club
Which is sweepy. We have a giant shrimp. We have a manly man, Aiden. He's not very manly. He has a little more estrogen than you can even throw a stick at.
We have Poppin, Exiled One Dog. We have Black RG on the ban list. We have Kevin. We have a concrete Larry IV. Team Alexandra.
We have a sack, LaBoub. Michelle Bigums. We have art. We have Ginger's Revenge, which is probably Q, I'm guessing.
who will never, ever, ever be unhidden.
We have Banana Eatin' Chimp.
We have Alex Mayers, but I think it's a fake one.
We have Gary Coleman.
We have Chicken Bunny Aiden.
We have Brandon's Massive Tits.
Allied Master Computer.
Visectomy Vic.
We have Dave Fitzgerald.
We have Ignorance Is Bliss.
We have Charlie.
Copium Dealer Aiden.
Psyche loves turds.
They David you help you to help admin white girl Aiden James
Arthur is hidden are to choke
Kevin
Concrete Larry the third concrete Larry the second concrete Larry the fourth concrete Larry the fifth concrete Larry the sixth concrete
Larry the seventh
Eldo is hidden. He should not be stop holding hiding Eldo. This person that hides Eldo is in trouble
Okay, Aiden the completionist, Christina's hidden, that's fine, Gary RR, we have Droopy
Face, Bung Bung, the troublemaker, I mean Brandon Q doesn't have to be hidden, he can
just be not a mod.
We have Mike Hunt, the thing that was, this Hunt, Mads Droopin, and Droopin at Well, thing
The thing that could possibly be triple 9-11.
That doesn't sound very good.
We have Juice, the one of many ETC simps.
Sidewalk Chalk 2.
Adair Gerald's.
The Liar.
Liar's Lie.
Bay Clips.
Blogger, why is Blogger here?
I don't know if Blogger's sitting, okay.
So nice Tamicha.
Jim J. Haywire.
Twack.
Red Balloon.
Olive Garden, Green Aiden, Hall, that is.
Cheese, Shorter Aiden, Uncle Phil, a Papa Phil.
And there's that Ben Margera's uncle's picture.
Norman Bates, Chat Rapt, Conqueror.
I mean, am I going insane reading these names?
It sounds like a mental asylum ledger.
No, Casey's not okay.
Casey, you need some mental help today.
You're out of the chat.
Yeah, Casey's never donated anything. Oh, actually he donated $5 so you can get back in the chat
What is he complaining about my cat? My cats are fine. Absolutely fine
They're just meowing. It's funny because it's true. Yeah, okay, Casey, can you donate $5 for my cats?
Oh, yeah, you can't because you don't have any money. You're poorer than me. I
The first thing I buy is cat food. I can prove it to you.
Huge, enormous amount of dry food.
Here we go, baby. Let's see if they all run over to eat it.
Oh, they're not even running to eat it
because they're not hungry
because they have plenty of food there.
Dummy.
Don't talk about me feeding my cats again, KZ.
And unless somebody is sending a donation or something,
don't need to mention like what's going on here,
like really, unless you're sending like, you know,
oh, it looks like you're kind of hungry.
It looks like you need a cigarette.
Here's a dollar or something like that.
Don't say, oh, don't beg for money for it.
I mean, people are just so dumb, you know, it's like.
If I need something, if you ever hear a closed mouth, don't get fed, right?
Sometimes you just get to ask for things, right?
Mackenzie, go ask for one of those little bundles with a blanket and a, you know, wet wipes in it for yourself.
I mean, jeez, that doesn't work on me.
Oh, we have a grassy-ass coming up here, that's welcome.
I'm sorry I didn't post the link yet.
Hi, Lola.
Okay.
Well, Casey, it's better than what you begging online is crazy. I didn't ask for anything. I was just accused of it
Oh shit. Okay, Zimples go fuck fucking low-key your fat
Your fat girlfriend. That's in a wheelchair and don't come ever come back. Okay. How about that fat retarded down syndrome girlfriend
And a psychopath perfect match for YouTube
It's all mean you big if I didn't ask for anything. I was telling KZ to shut the fuck up
But if I want to eat bag
Have you ever heard a closed mouth don't get that no you haven't
Because I guess you just get everything into you on a silver platter without even having to ask for anything zimples
Most hosts ask for something even Logan Paul is selling millions of dollars of acidic water
Hi
I'm sorry I'm playing with my baby cat
Yeah, I had a great birthday yesterday and
Good friends Jamie and Nancy also sent gifts and you know
And I defended Jamie because they're trying to say that she used AI when everybody has seen her
And and me and Brandon are okay. I guess it was my fault because I thought that he was in Alex's chat
Talking about the money because she said we were all
What was it that?
Conspiracy were extortion
Extortion yeah, and I told him leave her alone or whatever and that's why we got into it because I thought he was in her chat
starting crap
Yeah, and he told me it wasn't her chat. She did a a picture of your chat. It was your chat
He was in I didn't know I didn't know I mean I I
Yeah
Because I
When he typed that I said no as I don't say that because he said oh it's paid a psyche that I'll do that
I was like don't I was like don't do say anything like that. She'll say I'm extorting her or it's my fault or something like that
Was a mod in the chat?
just because I'd beg him a mod so he wouldn't be kicked out immediately, you know, and then
hit it and stuff. Okay, shut up. Shut up, Zimples. I don't care. I don't care. You're
glad the impaler. You're just as bad as Lady Bathory, in my opinion, so I don't care what you
have to say. There's a Lady Bathory. Yeah, if you want your opinion read, you can go ahead and
donate. I'm not looking at your comments ever again, Zimples. Anyway, there's so many people
that just want to insult me for free. They said up here, they just insult me for free. Like, they'll
just say, and they think it's like, okay, and then they go, oh, you kicked me off the shit out of the
And then even, I mean, I'm like, of course,
they're insulting me, not doing anything for me,
taking advantage of the whole thing,
thing that is yesterday.
Oh, let the guy talk.
It was like, it was Allied Master Computer talking,
whining over and over, sending me text messages,
and thing that is sitting there smiling.
It's like, okay, you run a chat thing that is.
Have I ever said you run a thing
that I was running for?
I don't know.
He sits there on other panels for hours and hours and hours and tries to stop him.
Yeah, right, for hours, hours and hours.
I've never seen anybody like live on panels like that.
Yeah, I know, I've seen him.
Yeah, I mean, it's like, they're so judgmental at these people.
How can they be so judgmental?
Have you ever seen a photograph of them?
Besides like I know most of them don't even have a picture for their avatar and they sit there on voice changers
and and this and this and they just oh they sit in Cates and and beat us and
Samans and just sit there and judge like they're at the popular school at the
That's no bodies. I mean shit
Different in real life that I hang out with them like yesterday. I had fun
You know, my family, but they want to continue celebrating this weekend and
So I guess we are and my brother's buying a new another Mercedes AMG
I'll show it to you. He showed me the picture where he's gonna get it and my sister is gonna keep his and he just bought that what?
four or five months ago
They're into those kind of cars me. I just like it simple like my dad likes
And you know they became like my mom, but it's got to be something really nice and expensive and where Rolex is
I was never like that
Well, you know my dad like nice watches and stuff
But he would always like he'd be like he'd give me like a fake Rolex that he got for his friend that he bought on China for
$10 on the street
He'd be like it might be real. We have another guest on me. His name is Western Union. I think it might be Arthur
What do you think? No, that's Arthur. I can't stand he's he's he's so two-faced. He's always you know
I've seen him join KK's talking about Sam and right after he was on Samans, you know pretty much glazing him. Oh
He was like, he wants to give Samman the longest, hardest blow job he's ever had.
Right? Yeah. I mean, they were just bashing him the other day. They were talking about him.
He goes right over, but Sam, and he's based in it. It's like, oh, you little bitch.
Are you just like, Earth, did you suck? Like, you know, even Samman, he can't stand them.
It's just a little bitch. I guess. Yeah. Arthur, I'll hang up on him.
Yeah, I don't like that guy. He's just all over the place. They said that they already are trying to put his docks out or something
I heard the other day that he's a
It might be sweet, it might be sweet peas sometimes she comes on. Sweet pea?
Hey sight
Hi, it's sweet pea. I'm grateful. Hey, sweet pea. Hey
And so I've been hanging out with my cats this morning. I mean, yeah, I was out all day yesterday and yeah
Oh, and then those two friends sent me beautiful gifts again. I've never given them money
We're fine. I mean people always try to cause fights between us and I defended Jamie if you look on my
My YouTube that's her. She's all if she's been on panels and she's a beautiful, you know young lady
Thank you, and she had her channel her own channel and she always did
Panels and she never used any filters like the other person that would when she joined her panel
So that other one is attacking at her. No, no, not beat. I'm talking about the Ella person
Yeah, I mean she's the one using filters and
Yes, and then she's putting a filter like crystal taught her to use to make it look like she's you know looking practically like
No, like
Who is it? It's uh
Gosh, um Britney Spears
Leave her alone. Leave her alone. I'm serious. You remember that
Yeah, yeah, I mean, it's crazy and and I mean and now she's trying to join a Alex's
Angry campaign or whatever and I'm just done. I don't like to be
Used lied to and I don't like the back and forth. I've never seen that before
Never liked that, you know, and I'm just so done and giving chances and I gave one person one more chance
You know and I don't see them going back and forth. Actually, they said something defending me
Well, I mean, can you give me a chance? I have no beef with you. I am there
Yes, Western Union. I'd like your name. I like your name Western Union
Just call them Western Union. Yeah, I like that. Yeah, I'll call them Western Union. Yeah, sure
I have no beef with you. I am next. I don't know why you were shitting on me earlier
When I don't know your name unless you have another count that it was
Sweet oh my no, I don't have it in she was sweet pea sweet pea with this song. Yeah, no
It's Christine there. It's Christine there. No, I don't talk to Christine. I heard about her. No, I don't I don't why
Oh my god. She's there. Oh my god. We're caught. We're caught. We're caught. That's the best. I haven't. I didn't talk about her. I don't know the lady. I just see, you know, whatever. I'm selling my house for a couple of new ports. What do you want? New ports. I don't smoke cigarettes.
Yeah, man, it's just crazy what's going on. But you know what, like real life is good and it's good to, you know, do real life like yesterday on my birthday. I was out all day celebrating.
Happy birthday.
Thank you. I have sure the same birthday as Princess Diana.
Oh.
July 1st. You can check it out.
Yeah, the same and Pamela Anderson too, but I don't know how old she is it's July 1st
But what you know what your birthday also marks what after the year has gone by
Yes, I know
Yes, I always knew that yeah, I was born in the summer
Actually, I was supposed to be born in in June for but for some reason I don't know it happened on July 1st
Is that I was born and Alexander was also born one seven and you're born seven one and so we're like we're like
That's what you said the same, you know, and I was talking to friend and that's the same thing with them
They said well seven one and mines one seven and and I didn't realize that till they said it
It's like oh, you're right, you know, it's just a number switched around
Right, I know but
raw
All of hogan on the line now, and you know what thank you brother
When I went out with some friends though, you know, it's weird because one of them I've
already known for years and he didn't realize he didn't know my birthday was July 1st until
the 1st of July.
He goes, wait a minute, Karen, because he said happy birthday and he goes, wait a minute,
your birthday is July 1st.
His is too and and in that weird I never knew that about him
I mean, you know, I hadn't been in contact with him for a while
But even when we partied in all those all those years. I never knew his birth date
Next we have another cult member in the in the room. It's it's it's mr. Extendo
Joker oh
Okay, I need a sub to him because he said he was going live the other day and I had to go
I just got darned watching lady boys
Watch lady
Is it a movie or are you watch them on like you know a pornography? I always knew you were gay
No, so like if a lady boy, it's with a woman is that gay? No
Can you know what a lady boy is Karen
I don't know. I don't know. It's a boy. It's it's not it's not what something with boys really is it but an Asian gender
The woman is like transgender. Oh, I've never heard of that. Yeah
Oh boys, but they actually they can change and like Thailand they kickbox and stuff like that
They're like real tough, but they also like they're like, you know, the sex industry too
But a lot of people in Asia are so feminine looking that a lot of them they do yeah
They they already look feminine looking, you know, man. Take care of their skin too much
Mm-hmm good
The pearls I heard that there's some kind of thing with that with that Korean foreskins that they put on the skin
Have you heard of that? Yeah, I think I was said on your live. They were yeah, I never knew that Andrew Bullock and Ellen do that
I think
Is that sick?
What?
That's weird.
So, like, I just got into this debate, like, if a lady boy is with a woman, is that gay?
I like to talk about this.
Okay.
So, Luya, can I ask you about this guy?
What if there's a female to male here?
Have you ever heard of Buck Angel or something like that, or there's other ones, like Justin
Bieber.
He was born a female.
Now he's a male character.
Joe confirmed gay.
Yeah.
so it would look like a lesbian thing right because it would be like a lady or looking at
two women but it's actually a woman and a gay transgender is that gay?
Yeah, huh a gay transgender. Let's say if it's a man. He's
Transdanger to a woman or
He's just but he's not not not full surgery. He's just like a he's like a biological male
But he's a presents as a woman and then there's a regular woman presenting as if you know as a female
And so is that a lesbian is that considered gay?
It's a man a woman though ultimately
Yeah, but ultimately you know his thoughts are, I'm a bitch, and I'm fucking a bitch.
I imagine it's more masculine, and there's like the females and males are like all big.
I don't know what you call that.
I don't know.
Bi-sexual?
Have you ever seen Buck Angel?
I don't know what you call that.
I'll show you a picture of Buck Angel, Buck Angel.
I don't know.
Bi-sexual?
Now real quick, IMX, this is Arthur.
I don't know what you call that.
I don't know.
Bi-sexual?
OK, Arthur.
I don't know what you call that.
OK, I just didn't know, because I remember one time
I don't know.
Bi-sexual?
I don't know what you call that.
you tried to go at me or something, you know.
Bi-sexual?
I don't know.
But let's be clear, though.
I do go at everyone playfully.
You do?
Oh, OK.
I don't know.
I have a doctor.
Today, so.
That's why I wanted him to do his sweepy as Christine,
because those kind of, they were my heart.
Those those and I always forgive him for everything every horrible thing he said about me and he said many terrible things about me
You have as well. I know but oh wow. He's got a vape. I got I got to get one today
I finished mine the other day the fogger. This is a fogger. Oh the fogger
Now for the record, I still stand against everything psych has done
Everything everything I haven't done one good thing Arthur
Here's a picture of look angel, so this is a female to male. What do you think? Okay?
That looks like a dude.
That looks like a guy.
Yeah.
She was born a woman.
She does porn and stuff like that.
Oh my God.
That's a woman?
Looking like that?
The body, you know?
Yeah.
She's a porn star and stuff.
And I saw her in Mojpovic probably in the 90s.
Yeah.
She's done a ton of adult films, but she has guys fuck her in the movies.
And it looks like gay porn.
Oh, I'm sorry.
It looks like gay porn.
But it's actually, then you see the vagina and it's like, okay, this is strange.
Wait a minute.
See he had he whatever has a vagina. Yes, and look like that
Well, how did they become looking like that if they didn't have the full-on surgery?
I think that changes because women can't have the surgery
I mean, there's no really good bottom surgery for women that they can use like, you know
They can have like, you know, the labia kind of enlarge a little bit if they want to but what they can do is
Do male hormones and then they?
Basically get the body hair. They get the facial hair. I didn't know that. Wow
Yeah, they gave him a something to use down there. I didn't know that they don't can't change that part
They take enough trt or whatever then they will have a mustache
Yeah, I mean it's really big we're didn't must I love me Jesus
Better must send didn't joker. I mean it's like she really can't but it's okay because look at the thing of all the testoffs
That must be a ton of testosterone is flooding into
Plus probably had some a natural testosterone, but it's your fiancee. They have a transgender there, too
No, I don't watch that show
Okay, I forgot the guy's name, but it was like in South America and he actually like
He told the woman, and then she...
I mean she didn't know she I mean she did find out on Facebook
He said go look at my Facebook and then she found out that it was he was born a woman
But she didn't care. I think the guy's thing with almost like Isabella is Isabella and something
Well, she's this guy's picture. He's a black guy. Mm-hmm. I know the difference
Between this guy. Yeah, I like yeah, I'll see if I can find a find his body like he's real musky
yeah, so here here this is the guy 90 day fiance and
He'll be kind of shocked probably
So this is what he looks like.
Would you ever be able to tell that this was born a woman?
Oh gosh, Jordan, hold on.
I'll just share my screen here.
This was born, actually, I have to be careful
because there's might be the nudity hook.
We just save it as a JPG.
I'm so sorry.
Okay, it should be saved as a JPG.
Downloads?
Okay, it looks right.
Okay, hold on.
Try one more time.
This is a, oh, here it is.
Yeah, here we go.
There oh, wow
Now that's actually a man or a woman
Yeah, I think the nipples looks yeah like it like belongs to a woman, but the rest of the body is like wow
Yeah, like a man's body it's a man's body with
Yeah, well, that's been so but so Joker would you ever would that be too gay if you hooked up with like a
Transgender like female to male
Yeah, that would be kind of too far.
We do, no way.
They have, like, they have hair.
I wouldn't be against them.
Like, I could be friends with them, but no, I wouldn't go do that.
I wouldn't, no.
Joker doesn't want to be with a woman with a hair on her armpit.
So bigger mustache than him.
Yeah, I don't want to find a woman with more mustache.
Yeah, and the guy has to have a real penis.
Joker all of a sudden is, like, being pinned down.
I've been down.
Did you guys see, sorry, did you see they're making the Odyssey movie?
Oh, they're making an Odyssey movie.
But they are?
I love the Odyssey.
It's got Elliot Page in it.
It's got Elliot Page from Juno.
Oh, okay. Yeah, Ellie Page is, yeah, Ellie Page is a female, right, but she looks like
a male.
She's a female that turned male.
Okay. Yeah, she's turned male. And so she's in the Odyssey. Is she playing a modusias
or, you know, the Cyclops?
She's playing some side character. There's also going to be a African-American woman
and they're calling her the Helen of Detroit.
Okay.
It's got the most negative reviews out of any medieval movie ever.
Because the Odyssey's a hard one to do because it's so long. I mean it's like that. I mean it's like what what are they gonna focus on?
You can focus you can make like 10 movies out of that out of the Odyssey, right?
And yeah, it's still have too much detail. I think do something about the witch or something like that
I don't know witches on islands are always good
Directed by Christopher Nolan from Batman. Okay. Oh really from that. What's the name called cuz I love the Batman movie
That was a kid, huh auto what the Odyssey the Odyssey
Yeah, I'm gonna get I can download it right now. It's showing me it's in the torrents. I
Use IP vanish to you know, you got to cover your IP. I
Was the chat saying you somebody in the chat said they like being handcuffed what?
And cuffed
Sike what i love about this i got the wireless or whatever through this company and it's super fast it's so now my brother he brought me a see a new 65 inch TV.
He's gonna send somebody to install it and all without wires and then he told me to instead of me transferring my movies into the into what he called the little connection or whatever.
And I use that I connected to the TV or take it to friends and play it
He said I don't even need that that type of connection because the TV that he brought me
It's a huge Samsung TV. He says it's wireless too. And since I have wireless service all it does
It picks it up on the TV any movie that I get for the record. I do not stand with everything psyche has
Okay, they're moving on with our lives. Brandon's not in the home jail.
I just have to say that every time because...
I don't agree with you having Brandon Q here.
Are there a peace affiliate with this show, then so are you, okay?
That's how it goes.
Negative, because I just said what I said.
You're on the show.
Literally, you're on the show right now, Arthur.
But I'm saying what you did is I'm against.
Well, don't say that on my show.
I don't like that.
You have to support me and glaze me a little bit like you say I'm man.
He hates you.
Negative.
Now real quick, Joker.
Hey, get out of here.
Wait, Joker.
I say one question.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Joker.
Yo, real quick there, buddy. I'm going to give you a little tip, all right?
So you go to the dollar store and you can buy yourself like a cheap set of razors.
Get out of here!
You ain't seen my man alone.
He doesn't shave unless he wants to shave.
He's so sexy because Burt Reynolds must have.
Thank you, psych.
Thank you.
Welcome.
I'm going to protect my friends, too.
Because Joker, like, you know, so I don't know if you heard about this Amber story,
but the other day I did it, Amber came on and I was talking and kind of griping about,
like, when, you know,
people would say, Oh, well, Joker looks like he's a child and stuff like that.
And so I said, I know.
So I said, you look young, really young.
And and so do I, though, too, in real life.
I'll help you too, but but so so I said to Amber, I said,
Amber, if you had a 26 year old son, if you if you if you Joker was your son,
I said, if he was 26 years old, like, how would you feel if he was
just interacting with somebody on YouTube on a panel?
And then she, you know, I was like, because everyone's like, oh, people make a big deal out of like, you know, and so I was like, and then she said, well, I have a good sense of humor, so I'd probably say, wear protection.
or something like that.
Whoa.
This is so twisty.
Hey, I don't like the lies.
That's awful to do that.
I mean, twist things.
Yeah.
That's, yeah.
That's, I don't know Amber, you know, I've never, I don't think I've even talked to her,
but I remember that one person who called my family or my brother, you know, months ago
Um, said that I was friend, something about YP2, um, I don't know, whatever that site
was and for him to look at it, because I was hanging out with my best friend and she didn't
say Amber.
She said a different name and whatever the rest of her username is a red yeah it's at Larry the method and I said there I don't know of any Larry the method and I don't know Amber because I did think of that name out that they mean her.
But I've never communicated with her anyway. I've done a couple methods in Larry. No. Oh, this is a person online. Oh my gosh
I know hey Rose Rose just don't respond to them like saying that we know
But so just just hide those people okay, I and you're supposed to help me. I can't help you right now
So I'm doing a panel. Okay. Thank you
You mods are busy today
Thank you. Thank you. Love to my mom. Yeah, but um, I mean it's getting crazy
There's like a lot of accusations and stuff being thrown around and it's like also the the meth ring the extortion
I think every every mailbox every day. There's not been a pound of meth
As long as I can remember. I don't even really know what it looks like the only thing I've seen close to that was
What was it the outbreak that movie? It was a series about meth heads
Oh, it's breaking bad breaking bad. That's what it was. Yeah, I forgot the name
I remember that and I thought wow
I mean when they showed him all you know way higher, you know
They were like really messed up and that's something I would never touch
It kind of looks like a rock candy. Yeah
I've done well, so it kind of looks like the coke I've done crack before though, you know, not
This is a rose. This is pink. Yeah. It looks like this and the good stuff is pink because I had a
bedroom but no this is just just a rose quartz crystal actually so don't worry about it.
Well, yeah, I'm glad I never touched it
You know, I've never been around it never want to do speed because it affects it decays your
Frontal cortex to where your contractual cortex will have to become dependent on the stimulant right and without
Right, I mean it's like a zombie or it's like I mean it kind of like in a fryer. Oh, I've seen that because
my weed dealer, me and him, we went to go get some chicken and he parked. I was getting ready to
get out of his car, we wouldn't go in and he said, before we get out, look at that guy because I was
seeing some guy that looked really wasted. He was standing there against the post and
he looked like a zombie like you know where he was.
I didn't say anything and he pointed pointed him out and he's you see that guy I said yeah
I said what's wrong with them and said those those methods that's where they go in that corner because
there's an open space between the chicken place and another building and he said they hang out there
and when I got out of the car I saw there were a bunch of them and they were like wasted like
they were like zombies
Look at there's these robots in my chat that are starting to see bros see you you showed a weakness
And this is a lesson to you when you show a weakness like oh, they're saying this they're saying that
When you say that that they're just gonna keep saying it like over and over again
So now you have to keep hide all those people, okay?
And don't stop saying that but they're messing with her. Yeah, they're saying she's a child and stuff like that
See, that's I hate people like that trolls. That's why I I don't know. I'm just sick of the trolling and
You know, it's just crazy. You should two weaknesses rose when you said you set up here
I'm not a minor. What the fuck instead of
And then you said for me to help you psyche help to
Hell bro, I will I'm doing I'm doing an interview with stars of the of the of the you know the YouTube
I mean, I'm not a star. He is Joker is he's well known. Someone just called me a gooner
What is a gooner? I've never heard that word before. A goonie. What is that? I don't even know what that means. That's new
You goon like this. Yeah. Well, and you know what a goon? Oh, wow
That's yeah, there's something called a goon face like here's one of mine
And that that means the face you make when you have an orgasm
The goon face the goon face, but what is grooming? I don't understand this grooming thing
I mean, I would love for someone to come comb my hair. It's a mess
Isn't it just me combing someone's hair? Why is it associated with like, you know
It's like I'm about to make some lunch. I'll see you. Oh
Okay, bye. Bye. Bye. He's abandoning us. Where did Arthur go? I scared him away with the grooming talk. Fuck
Arthur I kicked off Arthur because I did I kick off Arthur? I don't know. Yeah, I think you did
I don't know he was saying he's what didn't want somebody up or something or I don't know
It was just yeah, I mean, he's um, he's been like, you know saying, oh, you know
You know Brandon Q Brandon Q psyche boycott psyche and he thinks he boycott him and now he comes back like you know nothing
But it's okay. I the only thing I the only reason I like Arthur is because he was an amateur wrestler
He was and and he also he's part Filipino and I like Filipino people and
He also and he's kind he is cute. He's a cute. He's a good-looking man
I would he has a nice back side and stuff and then and a nice face nice nice pleasant face
Mm-hmm, and I like a lot of things about him actually. I mean, I was like I really would like to marry him. I mean, but I
Thought you were gonna marry ghost
Oh, I was trying I was trying to pass him off to you. You know, he did try to call me late last night
Uh, you know, it's I don't know. I'm just being really careful with these people and I've been blocking some calls
Especially people YouTube that do have my number. He's seen cool and everything, but
Here's what he did. I think I think I know what he did. He said, oh come join me here and then he gave you a link
He's not there
Not there and it was a link to betas. I mean you were backstage at betas. Yeah, that happened
I was at betas backstage and you know, and then he put me in another one
And uh, I don't know who it was and he wasn't there
Yeah, I mean it's like
And it's a direct chat. It's the direct live link that he gives out
It's like you don't even know where you're going as soon as you click on there. You can't see a channel
You see that you're already
In in the live he was at the beat is one, but then she I mean I heard her say oh ghost
No, you can't come up. Oh, and then she didn't go to psychies and she's like, oh and she's like it
Here's INX. Well, she's like, I don't think this is a real INX
She thought it was and then you disappear. No, it was me and this is the name I used
That was gonna be a porn bomber or something like that
But I didn't hear that part because I dropped out immediately. It's like where you put me at and then he put me in some other weird and
Place and they were docking each other and they were cursing each other out. It's like what the hell? I don't need to be here
And they were like who are you? I said, uh, I don't even know you. I said go sent me the link
He said well, he's not here
Ghost will say, hey, start alive.
He'll say, for me to start alive because I want to come up and then I'll be like, well,
I feel like streaming, but okay, I'll start one so you can like, you know, and then maybe
like, you know, do, and then I come here and I sit here for like 30, 40 minutes and he
doesn't even show up.
There's no way like I mean
He's in other chats or I guess or other lives. I don't know. I just didn't like that. It's don't tell me
You know, hey, you're in there. Are you in there yet?
And I'm in there by myself with him not even showing up for a long long time
I know it's like it's like say. Oh, it's like saying to somebody. Oh meet me my friend's house
I'll be there later. You don't know any of them. Just walk in
And, you know, it's like, it's like, no, you need to be there to introduce me to everybody,
maybe feel comfortable, and I'll see how I figure it out. You don't want us to be dropped in the
line. And he drops you. I mean, you can see this, he's like real conflict heavy, like so he likes
to just fight with people. So his, his chances are just the debating chats and these fighting
chats and these crazy chats and so, so I look, he's, he's a good, he's a good heart. He's a good
person. I kind of yelled at him a little bit. Oh, we have Arthur back here. Arthur.
Okay, yeah, Arthur is cool. See, you have a friend, Arthur. We have cool people in my chat, Arthur.
Yeah, he seems cool. I didn't know him.
You don't want to say, though, I do not stand with what?
No, Arthur, Arthur, you should say that about...
I should say that every time I do.
And I have to say, Arthur, if you ever want to blow, you know who to come to.
You know what the truth is and if you look it up and it's at random doesn't have any arrest for for doing those things
You know, I guess he sometimes goes into that app thing to you know to tell kids to get off and a long time ago
I guess he was drunk and all they show is a clip and he wasn't hitting on the girl
He was just going along with the combo, but nothing came of it
Yeah
That's I mean there we go are throwing that's pretty much still don't talk to kids and because people will say
Oh, you're grooming because gamble used to have a kid
It was Daniel that he would and and it's when you Google him
It'll pull it up because that's how I saw it a few years ago. Yeah
I mean the kid was arrested for child pornography and stuff, but really he was a little kid then this was in during COVID
So he's older now. Yeah, I didn't know that
Yeah, her kid had like a young girl on the other day like a young girl like I don't know if that's true
I mean Brandon said that like she had a kid on her panel and stuff
Um, I think I saw a little bit of that and uh, no it was just a lady with the really high voice and
Didn't let her on she just had her like black screen to see who it was or they were trying to porn porn bomb
And she did not let her up. She didn't let her up
She might have let her
I don't see was he see that's the thing you can't really do like what he says he like has these
Scandals with other people and like like he was sending pictures of people like this picture of clumsy
He's like oh, I found this picture of clumsy on like a
Gay-whip website and Arthur look at this picture of clumsy found this website. Is this clumsy?
Hold on. Let me see. Oh, no, I gotta go to YouTube
You're telling if that's clumsy
I don't know it kind of it kind of looks like him and like an old picture. Maybe I don't know
I don't really know clumsy. I mean it's missing
I don't I mean that's the picture that I was posted
But I think I found the video where that picture came from and everything is taken out of context because look at the video
Here we go
So that it that looks like him
I don't know it was a Latino man just blowing up a balloon and it made it look like he had a ball gag in his mouth
I
Have his phone number you want me to give him a call I'll ask on the door
Yeah, let me ask it. Yeah, ask him if that was I want to find out if he's an easy gay escort
I might be interested in buying a services
He's a gay escort. Yeah, that's a brand. I don't know. Yeah, man
Yeah, yeah, but I don't want to talk to him. You know, he just
Yeah, you ask him
But anyway, I'm going to, I'm getting ready to go, uh, we're obsessed with Starbucks, so I'm going to go to Starbucks and plus plus those two friends gave me some nice gift cards too for Starbucks and Jamie. Yes. They gave me a bunch of that and great gifts.
I'm waiting on the delivery. They took pictures. It's beautiful. A bunch of gifts because they go, they buy stuff from a really nice expensive places and you know, it's yeah.
So it's on his way and then a bunch of Starbucks because you know we do the that this app to send Starbucks to each other
But it was like a gift card
Right for that. Yeah, and a gift card for something else though, too
But yeah, they're they're great and they've never taken advantage me or asked for money and never
Never that's a gish
No, not Gish. Oh, oh, no, it wasn't Gish. It's two other people. I'll say their names Nancy and Jamie
And they're not involved with this drama so they don't come on that you know
They mostly do real life and they'll watch a little bit of stuff
But yeah, they're not involved in this and I don't know what they were gonna go on panel about
Somebody barb I guess but yeah, it's what's it gonna do just gonna bring more drama and BS
And you know, so they're not so they're not gonna do that
Brave little toaster is moderate. I did see brave little toaster as a channel
I really recommend checking out brave little toaster channel. If you don't mind I moderated just to protect you in this
Are you gonna show? Oh, you know what share that video that I just shared about Lindsey?
Okay, that's interesting and the mention of Gamble now
I did post a clip of the short of the short heard just talking about Gamble
And then I shared the full video, but you might want to check it take it from my shorts
It's the recent one. I just put up
Okay, well, check out your shorts. Yeah, and have fun and stuff and
Yeah, I'm gonna see so so grateful
Okay, I'm gonna look one of your channel. Let me see great grateful 2026 2026
I mean, I don't know. I have a great great. Have you seen the the pictures?
She's showing of of betta and um and saman arthur
Who which one you a grateful has posted the long time don't keep showing that though, you know, it's please it's just yeah
Arthur might might know about Arthur doesn't know this gamble stuff
Yeah, but don't put it on your live. I mean it's you know
They're disturbing they're disturbing very disturbing photos they are no, okay, so
Let's see about Astro mom.
Let me see what your shorts it says.
Oh, I have Astro mom's picture, a couple of them.
So I didn't I didn't post her picture.
Well, it looks like you have some great shorts.
I'm going to I'm going to play.
Yeah, I have a really good shorts that doesn't have anything to do with drama.
Just stuff that I like and I share.
OK, I'm going to play your show.
I'm going to play some shorts of yours. OK. OK.
Let's just bring these up.
OK, and I'm going to share the screen.
OK. Hey, Arthur, get ready to.
Take off your shoes. Yeah. Let's see them. Okay.
Allowance is made for fair use for purposes such as criticism, comment, news reporting, scholarship, and research.
Fair use is a use permitted by copyright statute that might otherwise be infringing.
Non-profit, educational, or personal use tips the balance in favor of fair use.
We're gonna play it. Actually, do you want me to bring it up?
Yes.
Go bring it up. Get it. Go grab for it. Can we watch it? Why do you have this locked? Seed more. No, why do you have it locked? Seed more. Because you're creeping it. That's why my phone is locked.
That's Lindsay and Joe. Creepy. People's phone. Actually, your daughter's phone. Oh, do you want to go for two hours? You're wearing a top? You're trying to beat me out of someone. You're wearing a top?
Yeah, watch what they say about gamble. It's a short one. What watch what she says, but they're arguing right now
No, it did she just it's it's she's um if she freezes while she's doing the live and I think it's because
She said something about it earlier in the video
her connection freezes
reduce me to that.
But I'm drinking water.
Joel, servers and telling me on the side,
you weren't in those servers.
I was already there before.
And Wilbur posted videos recently proving
that you were in there.
And not just in there, but when you were in a little spat
with me or something, you were telling them
that you were selling my feet pics.
That you kicked me from your server.
So because I kicked you from my server
before I met up with you.
Well
No, just to play it it ends after the work that when she mentions gamble
Oh, see I sent him to gamble. She just said he
Can you rewind it a little bit? That's he asked about gamble. I think and she said that he asked for his big pig
Yeah
People shit about me and if he's coming back to me, I didn't give a fuck about your dick. I was already in those surfers
You can go and you can prove and go prove that I gave your dick paper is thank you
Here's the thing like
You know when I asked for Arthur's dick pic, it's because I really want to see it
I mean it's like and I was just for my private use when gamble
Gamble asked somebody for a dick pic. I mean, yeah, it's vicious and he wants to use it for blackmail
He wants to accuse and also if you look at Brandon's page. He shows the screenshot of that live where
Gamble was I think he was wearing like a string thing and bikini like women wear and he was showing his
Asked to a little boy. You can see that
background
Terrible it's so disgusting that no right and then he was in brandon's cat. Uh, yes, so he's stalking him and talking shit
I guess he was upset that me and him are good. I was the one that overreacted thinking that Brandon was in somebody else's chat
Saying same people money. I'm sorry. Speaking of stalking though. I mean, I saw this there's this woman
I'll just say her initials are am I'm gonna avoid saying her name right now, but her this is our am and she
She was like, you know on the street. It's a fruit street or something like that and she
She's on it. Did you see that?
Where on her? No, she's on his street. Oh, yeah, that's what he said that she said. She's an Albuquerque
She's not even saying she's showing she's on video there
Oh, I don't know. I didn't see that. I didn't really, you know, I was busy yesterday. It was my birthday. I'm 101 years old now.
You're 101?
I didn't know.
You can get a donation for each day.
I know.
Watched them. I watched this um this that thing to where amber has charges on her in yeah
I had New Jersey courts has the whole video. Yeah. Yeah, I saw it yesterday. Oh you saw it yesterday
Yeah, I saw it a long time ago. Yeah. Yeah, I mean I just thought for the first time yesterday and like then then good times
All pops up on it. I was like, oh, wow. I mean, it's like it was kind of interesting. Well, Amber came on dude to
Answer his questions about what she went through with her. So I don't know I didn't watch that part
I dropped off because I really don't know Amber. I just saw what he was showing
I I mean Amber's come to the show once and that made the dead and look like we're already a scandal. Oh my god
So, oh, okay, so I mean I want you to react a little bit to this often delete this episode. I mean immediately but
Don't delete it. Why because I mean so she might get mad at like you know or like try to look at these pictures
Well, I don't show her picture then I mean
Look who's the guy's Brandon strength. Yeah, I know all and then and that's not even me at all though, too
And no hair. Oh my my hair is down to a little over my shoulders, and it's very wavy
Well, I don't know and this is not you either. No, no. Yeah, that's yeah, I don't know. I don't know who that is
I don't look like that and I have a smooth face
I mean, you know, I look young and everybody even my doctors
No, that's not that's not me. I mean, I don't know what that is
I mean, she has quite an imagination.
Let me see.
Right, and then my eyes are practically hazel.
It changes from light brown to green,
like a light green, mostly out in light, in the sun.
Okay, so it says, imagine, just don't worry,
this might just be AI.
I think this is a short one, okay?
I just wanna show you this,
because she is on his street.
I think, here, check this out.
And Albuquerque is beautiful. It's very expensive there now very get a look it up talk about stocky
Yeah, I live in Academy of States over there, and that's a nice place
It was a lot of famous people and including this our next-door neighbor was a well-known
Chiropractor and he was always on commercials
And it was his daughter that was trying that was going to the Olympics to swim and they made a
like a smaller olympic size pool for her in the backyard and she'd train every day
live on fox one june 11 through july 18 shall we i love the weather in albuquerque except for
the winters it's just icy attempting to explore this very use for something that really then
in the chat of someone that I generously don't need a close to 1k to including material gifts
and demanding 2k from this and I never included the material gifts I sent people out it was quite a
bit a lot expensive stuff what you do in such a situation this nice little artwork imagine good
It also has really nice lawns.
Sometimes people might get them wrong.
Maybe it's due to my black privilege
that I've been treated so well by them.
I don't know.
I want you to take a good look.
You see?
Yeah.
Yep.
Oh, we have someone in the chat.
Be nice person.
It's so dry here. Yes, it is dry. I'm a very nice person
Especially now
I'm very polite
I was raised that way
I wasn't raised to be a motherfucking criminal
Nobody is I was raised
To deal with criminals. That's why there's so many attorneys in my family
Lots
We have attorney friends and they're all rapidly becoming a fan
of
In real life. It's the future. So I got to get going. I just wanted to come on here and say real quick
play stupid games
Win stupid prizes
Peace out
You know race horse Haynes was a friend of my mom's and his son he's an attorney he's I don't think he's as good as his dad
But he is my brother's best friend my older am I not older the second brother the nothing youngest
Because I remember my mom her friend, you know
She was celebrating her daughter's wedding and they had a few drinks and I mean that lady
You know she comes from money, you know because of oil and they pulled her over the police and she was
Freaking out and she called my mom and saying that they want to take take us all in because we've been drinking
And my mom called resource Haynes, he had his number.
And so he called the cop that was, you know, there.
And guess what?
He told him, go ahead and go, you know,
we're releasing you.
And so he let him go because of my mom's call.
Yeah, well, my uncle was a sergeant of this city
that I'm in, right?
And so it's like, you know, he was a sergeant.
Like he even got shot.
Like a little salute on they did this boat go out and like, you know, the 21 guns or something like that the 21
Loot and you know, they shoot these 21 guns out. Yeah, yeah
Yeah, but he was and he I mean he retired with the fourth
But it's like it's a little like small kind of peaceful police department for the most part
But you know he did get shot on the job once and like and that and he ended up like you know
retiring because
All the all the gun training you do just breaks down your shoulders over time, you know, and so really
They're pretty destroyed, but yeah, he died at the end. Oh, I'm sorry Rose Rose
Mess up her tattoo. So see roses an adult you need to be eating
have a tattoo so okay it's literally bleeding and go to the hospital please please I mean I
can't I don't know I don't like that idea of something bleak okay uh hey lennard do you want to see
lennard? oh I want to see lennard and lola lola looks just like kitty oh look at lola in the
curtain oh my lola she's hiding in the curtain but it's hard to see hey lola I'll show you here
Well, are you hiding in the curtains behind the curtains peeking at me? I see
Looking out the window like like boy cat
Okay, oh my gosh someone oh my gosh, we're not gonna let that person over just came up and go
You're lying and like if you have evidence proof or anything you can send it to my discord
You know we can join my discord and you can
They report but uh
Bad person not with the background versus backstage is a very inappropriate name
We are welcome to join my discord and send me any evidence any pictures any
any proof. Okay, otherwise I can't just bring you up unless you type in the
back chat where you're going to see too. I have some pictures that when I was
out and I came back home and then I see my peeking ease.
and kind of looking out the balcony window
and just sitting there in the middle
and two of my cats were right around him.
Isn't that weird?
It's like they get along like they love each other.
Oh my gosh.
Yeah.
My cats are getting along with Nora
because they're like the two ladies
and they have been a little rude.
Hey, Mr. Extend, I've joined my discord
because I have to, or like,
I'm my old discord like I got kicked out of it.
Like I can't and I kicked out of it. I just can't log into it
I like go accidentally like I put too much authentication on it. So I need I
Started a new discord and if anyone wants the new discord. Oh, yeah, send it to me
I'm gonna drop off cuz I'm my friends there and we're gonna go to the Galleria
and I'm gonna go to the Starbucks too.
Have fun.
Yeah, thanks a lot, but yeah, just go ahead
and text me the link for your Discord and I'll be in.
I'm forcing myself to drink another liter and a half
in water.
I was almost getting sick again recently and I woke up one morning. I couldn't even open my lips
It's like damn. Where's the chapstick and my doctor yells it means that you need to keep up with the water care
And that's the issue. It's like why do I get dehydrated so quick? I've never had that issue before last year
Well, here take care. Yeah. Okay. Love you too. We'll talk later. Okay. Bye. Bye
Who's this? I don't know if I know this person. This is a oh, oh, no, it's sick. Oh my gosh
I thought it was, I thought it was like, um, Belma from the Flintstones. Hold on a second.
Sig, are you okay? Oh my god. You look terrible. Oh no! How are you today? Oh,
I'm outside having sex. You almost like, I almost think you look a little bit better,
but then it's like, are you making yourself look weird? Well, no, you can't. We're out driving?
I'm taking drugs. It's so insensional. Is there a woman in the, in the car with you? Oh yeah.
She's sucking my dick right now.
Is that why you're smiling like that?
Or you can't?
Yeah, I'm smiling because she's sucking my dick.
Say, tell me what happened.
Why did this picture get posted by Aldi on my desk?
I don't know because Aldi's gay and he's obsessed with me.
He wants me to put my penis inside of his butt.
That's why.
Why do you look like that in that picture?
Is that right after the accident?
What accident didn't you like break your jaw or something? No, they're really talking about
Well, I've been why do you look like this lately?
It's just my that's how my jaw has always been. What are you talking about regular face?
That's my regular face. I
Was born this way baby a lifelong tragedy then bang
it's okay it's something it's something that I have to get surgically enhanced yeah it's
it's an intensive surgery imagine when you get all that plastic and it looks so much better
Do you think so?
I mean, do you think you'll ever get hungry?
I think I'll be all right without it,
but yeah, I should do it.
I mean, it's not just cosmetic.
Like, if I don't fix it, like as I get older,
it'll get worse.
Sick.
It's something that gets worse.
A plastic surgeon, you know, came into the cat
and they saw this picture.
Are you, oh, this person walking in the office.
Where do you think they would start with that?
A surgeon you're asking me what a surgeon's opinion would be. Yeah, where would you start on your face?
I mean, what would if you were a surgeon, I guess like I don't know
I guess if I was a surgeon. Well, honestly, I
Couldn't tell you even where to start. I don't know. I have no idea what surgeons do I
What I what I can tell you
What I can tell you that the surgeon that and I have spoken to a surgeon about this
orthopedic surgeon
What's it called orthodontic yeah, I've spoken an orthodontic surgeon about this
Yeah, it's a it's a six-month recovery. It's pretty gnarly. They've liar your jaw stuck
They basically break your jaw fix it. Why would you do that?
Why are you shut?
Yeah, your jaw is off.
The jaw is called an underbite
Okay, you're big right where you're the under part of your jaw goes over your top part
Yeah
Where you kind of look like a bulldog basically
Well, that's what you look like you look like you look like I'm one of those British bulldogs. Have you ever been to England?
Yeah, that's what it is. Yeah, well
Yeah, that's true. I've seen English women. They the ones I've seen do have absolutely horrendous teeth. This is true
Well, see if I was on a lot of drugs and alcohol
You might have a chance with me
Thank you for letting me know so I appreciate that you're welcome. You're interested come on over. You can you can sleep in the bed together. I
appreciate your
Every single night every single night you live together
Okay
Yeah, he's really hot like I'm what about his wife. What is she how does she fit in there? She's sleeping between you
She she's kind of just like she's just like chill about it. She's like whatever
300 below has sex with demons
She's like what a dean is like whatever. Okay, so what 300 gets fucked in the ass by men on the regular
So what does she and I respect Dina for that if she's sitting in the corner or contemplating which one of them to shoot first
Nah, she'd be wiling out. She'd be joining in and shit to be wiling out
Actually, I think they invited me to join in pulling out a big-ass strap on dick
Would you be interested in doing an Eiffel Tower?
Can we do a triple Eiffel Tower with Joker?
No, no, no, I'm sorry, sorry.
Yeah, with Mr. Thorough and Glow, you and me.
Well, Joker can come too if you want, so I mean, Joe, I'm not sure.
I'm not really interested in this, no.
OK, maybe next time.
OK, I won't do it next time.
I'm still a virgin, so I don't want to go straight into like what do you call this group sex?
Oh, you're still a virgin so groups are too hot. I'm still a virgin
I'm not in the rush to do all this crazy shit. I thought you've been with a lot of guys
That doesn't count. Okay. I don't okay. So that's that's a client has to be a woman. So you've been with no zero doesn't count
You've been with thousands of guys though. I think it doesn't make a difference
I mean, it's not like you're just a virgin like you know your buttholes seem like a lot of traffic
Nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah
You know miracles can happen psyche. I don't know what to tell you
She's like I'm not gonna make a promise
Okay
But that's not gonna make a guarantee for you
But what I will tell you is that miracles do happen
You ever you ever you ever done a Mexican wrestling with them with the skinny guy like you're the fat guy
And then there's a skinny guy you can be wrestling like oil at Mexican masks
No
No, no, I can't say I've done that. It's like you're not just on nacho Libre. I
Think that's more of a gay thing. I don't think that's some Mexican wrestling
Or what is the game? Well, you're Mexican and we're wearing the masks. I mean what more do you want?
Mexicans are Mexican cultures actually very homophobic. Oh, I love that about it. Oh my god
It makes it so much hotter when you have sex
It's very they're very homophobic the Mexican
Mexicans in America not so bad, but Mexicans in Mexico very homophobic
Unicorn or I mean Marie come right
Would you say about Mario?
We love that name. We love these in the word Marie cone
Right, I don't even know what you're talking about
Maricón, it means like, it means F-A-G-G-O-T in Mexico.
Maricón? Yeah, that means gay guy.
Yeah. But you know what they say when they sing?
You know what they say when they sing?
It is called you, it is called you maize.
You know what that means?
No.
It means corn.
I've never heard that used as an insult, no.
Maze means corn. I learned that in Peewee's big adventure when they when he goes to the Alamo to find his bike
But it's not in the basement because there was no basement in the Alamo. You know where there is a basement?
Come at Peewee. Didn't Peewee Herman go to jail?
because he was masturbating in
corn feeders
Yeah, that's when those were things he was arrested. He didn't really like spend time in prison for he just was arrested for it. Yeah
Damn, so they just let him go. Yeah. Well, do you think what would you think?
Do you know some shit that psyche would do 100%
Why would I go to a movie theater and jerk up when I can jerk up at home? No, it's not a movie theater though
It's a it's a one theater. Well, then if they're playing porn there, what do they expect people to do?
This is a fair point. Honestly, I have to agree with you
I
Heard that that in those porn theaters, it's just a hookup place for gay dudes
That's all it is have this one in New York where you like you look in this like this like room
It's like you look at these little little hourglass
Do you put in like a they put in like they call it if you put in pennies and stuff like that
There'd be some naked woman in the back there. Hey, do you like Arthur? I'm saying oh
What's up, SIG?
I actually don't.
What's up, Blake?
Remove him.
No, I hope him now
Remove him now
Told you how much I love his head psyche
Francis, I love Arthur and I don't like you sick
with his head
Arthur
I still have fondness in it for Arthur because he's been with the show for so long and he's like any and whenever I tried to
Like he wants me to fondle his ass more than he does Arthur
Now you went too far, Sig.
Bang!
Yeah, that works just a little too much.
Hey, you got too gay.
You didn't get too gay even for argument.
You went too gay when you said that you wanted to put your penis inside of your asshole.
What the fuck?
Sig!
Bill, dude!
Okay, I'll take him up.
No, no, no, no, no, no, bring him back.
Okay, okay.
Real quick.
Arthur, why do you want to put your penis inside of Psyche's asshole?
Why did you say that?
I'm not McQueen.
Yo, real quick.
That's gay.
Real quick.
Salmon, I do not stand with what Psyche has said or him having Brandon.
Stop kissing Salmons.
This guy is gay.
I
Waved the salmon flag brother, I'm sorry
Arthur yeah, you don't tell me what to do. Hey, why do you have kids on your stream?
Why do you mod kids? Why do you mod kids pedophile?
We have a child in your chat pretending to be an adult, bro.
Oh, I'll hold on my transmission.
Oh, hold on my tattoo.
Trying so hard to pretend to be an adult, bro.
You're fucking sick, bro.
What kind of fucking adult goes, oh, oh, sorry.
I was gone for a minute.
I had to do something with my transmission.
And then now it's, oh, oh, I'm laying here.
My tattoo artist is cleaning my tattoo.
You're a fucking weirdo, bro.
You got a minor mod, bro.
You're a sick fuck, psyche.
Damn, Psyche, how do you respond to the allegations?
Oh, I'm sorry, I just, oh, I had, I just, um,
I just went to the bathroom, someone say something?
He just shit his pants.
Oh my gosh.
So that's Brandon, I mean, it's like, that's so crazy
that he's like trying to cause all this problem.
But I'm getting called a pedophile, Brandon,
he, everything's come full circle in the world, you know?
This is what you get you used to have his back. This is what happens. I know he's turning on me like
What happens what did we tell you?
You're right. I'm on we told you remember. What's the name RG?
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry. Don't say sorry to me. Say sorry to RG
No, I'm not saying sorry to RG. All right you
Let's do this. I'll stop saying the whole, hey, I don't stand with what he, you know,
I'll stop saying that if, if, if, if you can say, and I quote, if you can say the following.
RG I bend the knee to you brother. I am sorry for everything and well, if you can say that I
Say I'll say RG. I really don't have anything in particular
Against you. I was go I was going back and forth that you because you're going back and forth with me and saying things about me
And so I don't know about your true identity. I don't care about it
I really don't care about what happened with the blind guy back. He's you know or for the Ali master computer
Yeah, I don't care like I'll let you on the panel again if you want to
I've got no hard feelings, but I don't like you said he'll let you touch his butt again
Yeah, that's fine if you want Archie, I'll let you touch my butt
Yo, thank you, I feel bad that you're gay
I mean, I'm gay and I can't even hook up with the hottest gay guys like you and Arthur.
Oh, don't show, I'm not.
I feel bad for gay guys like Psycho.
So you don't feel bad for other gay guys then?
I only feel bad for Psyche, because he's a little bit harder than me.
I'm like the only gay person that's dirty, that's like weird, that's like, you know...
Psyche would have sex with himself if he could.
What the fuck?
Well, that's a good point. Like, if I could suck my own dick, I might do that.
Psyche would prefer to have sex with himself.
What the fuck?
It's 2027, okay?
Like he's actually a very progressive figure
This is what the shows come to now
Well on that point Sam and I do not agree with what psyche has done or said
Especially you know, we're talking about what he's done with
I've been his back. I've not stand for that and I never will let that be known
Damn is never gonna date you. Thank you, but the same
We're not the branding you he's dating be the dude. What do you mean? Hey Arthur? You're a fucking creep
You just have to put a block switch to your hand
Know what happened on my phone this shit says the heat and it I can't even close the app
put it next to the ace. Take the face off of your phone. Yes,
brother. I'm stuck here now.
You're stupid retarded gay man. Yo, fuck you. Take the face off
of the phone, dude. I'm about to put your mouth on a curb and
let me stomp your head out. No, no, no, no. Idiot. I bought
from my whole penis in your ass. Bye.
What's your fucking mouth on a curb? Yeah, you got a big-ass job. Let me fucking break that shit
Let me American history X you real quick. You heard
Well, it's the shower scene. Oh, this thing is stupid, bro. So it's funny. This thing is
Thank you so much. I am stupid. I am yeah, you're Norton is hot in his but look great that movie
Anything to do with penis too, for a second?
Did you ever see Kevin Bacon's cock in, um, Wild Things?
Negative.
Did you see that thing?
Whoa, that was sick!
Yeah.
Whoa, he looks so different.
Have you guys ever seen...
Have you guys ever seen my...
Yeah, we've seen your one inch.
Hey, Johnny.
You ever seen my thumb-shaped head?
Yeah, stop doing that to your neck. I'm gonna do something else to your neck. You're not gonna like
You're gonna end up growing a third chin dude. Stop doing that
Hey, why are you letting Bruce Valance now?
uh sake you ever seen that blob fish like it's been circling the internet for years it's like a blob
of fish i have it i have the blob fish yeah it looks just like a yeah it looks like the blob
fish i'm having sex outside while you guys like a very inside it's like a very discolored fish
Don't even think you can have sex with that one inch of gay.
Thanks.
Is this you?
I have more sex than you.
Thanks.
Is this your picture?
That's why you're mad.
Hold on.
Let me see.
I got to say this shit.
Dude, I got a whole wife from.
Shut the fuck up.
This guy's mad that his wife would rather have sex with me
than with him.
Thanks.
That looks exactly like him dude, what the fuck I told you dude, it's just like the bluff is.
Yeah, okay, or you know what someone said, he looks like a goomba from Mario Brothers,
he looks like one of those, the, the goomba.
I didn't see him looking just like the fish, they look like a bug.
Why does this guy look like the gate guy?
Right, yo, fuck you mean you don't suck big?
You don't suck dick cuz you're a bitch
By are you a bitch?
That's why you suck dick
No, you said you said you suck dick because you're a bitch
nah, brother
Nah, brother. You you suck dick
Cuz you're a big
You play a brother
Now you this guy is gay
Like you are a key you are a key my friend you are a key to love to this gay guy
He wants to have sex with men
Bang bang Arthur doing yeah
I'll start a new wrestling team with you and we can come to LA and you're gonna start a gay
Wrestling team where everyone
No, I'm not gonna use your name. It's already kind of gay, but it's not gay
You know, it's like straight guys do it. They know it's kind of gay, but it's like they still love it
okay, so
We started in Mexico. We can be a tag team. We wear masks and stuff and then and then if we win
Because it's like, you know, if we win then we get to have sex and sing can't watch
Why are you gay? Yo, you guys have you guys ever seen the porn where where it's like a guy and a girl wrestling?
No, and they're they're like and then they're like and then the end they fuck each other
No, it's an episode of Black Mirror.
So there's an episode of Black Mirror
where these Black guys start playing virtual tenants
over VR and stuff, but then they figure out
they can fuck in it and so then they can fuck in it.
Couple that one of the yo psyche look at this day police officer. Oh, so you walk into a store. Yo psyche
I found I found your new boyfriend. Hey, shut up. Shut up sick. Shut up sick Arthur
You know I rejected this fucking loser, right? You know this dude. You know this dude would still be here
Yo, Carl, you're a fucking homosexual, bro. I can't even take you seriously because you're gay
At least psyche is gay, but he's like
Mentally disabled, so it's like he gets it fast
Bang why are you game?
You ever seen that video? Why are you game?
Like he is gay because this is lifestyle choice, and I respected
I'm not even gay. I mean, it's like, don't you have to have some gay sex to be gay? I mean, I don't get any sex, so I'm not gay.
He doesn't, he has gay sex for the culture. He doesn't even like having gay sex.
I do. I do just to feel like, you know, special.
He has gay sex just because it's for the cloud.
It doesn't make me feel special. It doesn't make me feel special. Where'd he go? Oh my gosh, he left. We'll see.
I will never ever oh my god
Last time I think maybe Brandon is just Rose. It's like trolling himself. I don't know. He's so complicated
I don't even care anymore. I mean, it's like, you know, but Rose I don't know. It's like you're not the best mod
I think I'll just have you as a regular chatter. Like I mean, I'm having enough problems with I think it's time to cut you off
bang
Rose, okay. You have been demoted. Oh, yeah, I just I don't I don't feel comfortable with my mods saying that in my chat
Okay, but what is your mod saying? I'm putting my vibrator on my clit. Oh
Okay, great
Yeah
And Brandon says backstage it's gonna get worse. So this is day one
I'm probably just him saying these things
I think it is I'm not really afraid of him because you know Alexander is like right down the range
gun oh
So he's like so he's like gay and he's having his gay fantasies
Being this you're fucking sick, bro. You have a child. You have a child in your chat. You fucking predator
You have a little girl in your chat. You have a child as a mod bro talking about sick shit, bro
You have a child as a mod, bro
Talking about vibrators and shit, bro. You're a fucking predator, bro
That's a fucking child, bro. If you can't tell that's a child, bro
You need to get the fuck off the internet you fucking sick fuck
You're fucking sick
Hey, you know that you're in a panel right now where there's a mob the only person that's typing in his chat is the 12-year-old little girl, bro
Well, right now I'm driving. I'm not reading to you. I'm using my chat too. She was in my chat too and she was like
Shut up say nobody gives a fuck you're ugly as a fuck look how ugly
You don't have a dick. You don't have a dick, bro
Why do you have a child mod prove damn saying that they're 12 in my chat?
So why do you have a child why do you have a child in your is a mod?
You're a predator, bro
You're a predator. Why do you have a child child mod? I
Hey and Arthur by the way, bro
This dude would still be glazing me if I didn't cut him off
I'm the one that cut him off. So don't act like oh, he whized up. Oh, he saw the truth
I cut this fucking weirdo off, bro. I cut you off, bro. I discarded
Get out
You're banned from the show forever. Never come back here. You sick fuck
Calling me names. Wait, wait. Oh my god. Someone's a mom. I mean, it's like what it'd be what? I mean
Is there nudity on the panel is there
Alcohol Bob no, but it's probably you trying to like make me look like I'm some kind of weirdo by like being that person
And I don't know I
listen
If I could, like, go and request ID from everybody in this chat, I would.
Thank you. Would you let, would you let your, like, nieces and nephews watch this stream?
I mean, it's like, it's not made for children.
It's made for adults.
I mean, it's a yes or no question.
And he said, that feels like,
I have some of the, some are in their thirties
and stuff like that.
So I mean, they can watch whatever they want.
I wouldn't like the kids, no, no, but it's like,
like the teenagers, I don't really care,
but they don't, I mean, not interested in the show.
But what they watch, I don't care who watches really,
it's who can participate in the stuff.
It's like 21 and over, right?
But it's like, I don't necessarily know who's,
Don't know they're trying to like frame me or something like that to make it look like I'm something
And it's like probably him just all doing it and like they say outrageous things because no
I could just tell there's something weird about her, but I wanted to keep her kind of like just keep your eye on things
I don't know. I don't know. Maybe I just do the wrong thing. I don't know but
Well, I don't know so anyway
Brandon's band Brandon you can't come on the pan anymore. That's a final straw and just because of that. I'm gonna play
This donor scribe video again
Of some footage that was very shocking and I want you I mean you can't respond to it on the panel anymore, but I want you
Say you can watch this too if you can this is a I don't know. I don't know. Yeah. This is what happened
recently
and
Look at your screen, okay?
I'm getting out of the car right now.
Okay, well look at your screen when you can.
I'm not playing music.
Well, what is it though?
Can you describe it to me?
It's a, you ever see the catch a predator?
Yeah.
Okay.
Okay, so this is a, this is that, this is that.
So this guy is a predator.
I'm a little bit helps the channel grow.
Thank you so much.
Bye.
Don't tell me what to do thing that could be.
Hey
Everybody's a predator
Hey, I've got it instead of the table.
I'd make some cookies first.
Yo, Psyche, check it out.
I'm in a wealthy neighborhood with white people everywhere.
No, I'm not.
I'm in there.
It's for you.
No, I'm not.
No, girl.
You know?
You bet.
Look at all the pretty white women.
That don't smell like hot garbage.
Quiet.
I'm glad that this girl's age won't be a problem for you.
Yo, what?
What the fuck?
Go.
Go ahead and have a seat right there for me, please.
I think your name is Brandon.
Tell me what you were going to do here today.
Uh, I was just hanging out with someone.
Just hanging out.
Yeah, bro.
And how old is the person that you
are going to hang out with today, Brandon?
Oh, she's 18.
18?
Yeah.
Well, that's very interesting, because I
thought that I heard the young lady say a very different age.
And I believe that she said that she was 15.
Oh, come on, bro, you heard wrong.
Oh, you're so right. I'm getting a little bit older.
My hearing is not what it used to be, but...
But, you know, my vision's still pretty good,
and I can read the chat logs that you had with the girl
that you were planning on spending time with today.
Yeah, I mean, she told me she was 18 and now.
Oh, really? Really?
Is that what the chat logs are going to read today?
Well, I'm not a fucking pedophile, bro.
I don't hook up with kids.
In a text you had, she said she was 15 years of age,
and you responded, oh, I don't give a fuck about all that.
You're a sexist fuck.
No, bro. You're taking it out of context. I'm not a panel.
Oh, you're absolutely right. And I should, I should add more context and read more of
what you were intending to do with this girl that you believe was 15 years of age.
I wasn't going to do nothing to, I wasn't going to do nothing with her.
Well, you can tell me if I'm making this all up. Now, I know you're a YouTube streamer.
Isn't this the guy that does kids?
Yeah.
Okay, so this is good
And who am I? Who am I?
I'm the African American woman that's going to put a stop to your shit right now.
You don't recognize? You don't recognize who I am?
No.
Well, that figure's considering a million deficient man such as yourself might feel so very inadequate, perhaps even terrified.
of a woman of an African American woman
of the success and repute such as myself.
Do you realize that I was in a porn parody
of the Cosby show?
I am here.
To stand up for the marginalized and oppressed such as myself, the people who have been the victim of vicious, hateful smear campaigns on the internet.
Are you referring to this gentleman here? This is the man that came to meet a 15-year-old girl.
Oh, many people nowadays are targeted in the internet for sinister and nefarious reasons.
And it's all for the sake of its own.
The problem, can you pause for a second if you don't mind?
and I am here to call you out today.
Sikey.
Okay, let me get this back.
You're here too.
I just want to say something real quick.
Yeah, wasn't it?
Man, that came to me.
I mean, I guess it's still here.
There you go.
All right, I mean, the problem,
I know this is a skit and this is like a joke or whatever,
but the problem with this whole like Predator thing
and like Diddy Epstein, the problem with this whole thing,
Is that people are selective about who it's okay? Who's okay? And it was not okay to do this shit
right
like
There's like like there's people that like they say oh, I don't even care if Michael Jackson if all that was true
I don't even care
Like people people don't like he gets a pass, but then some like what's this guy's name?
Yeah, the fucking Weinstein Harvey Weinstein
He's got he literally they literally put him through so many court cases that he fucking died
All right, Bill Cosby, you know, I mean it's like but there's like also like I'm saying like
You know, and it's like I've been just on sexes, but it's like, you know, beautiful women can get like
Oh, yeah, beautiful women. They're just angels. They're just angels. They couldn't do no wrong and if they do wrong
There's a reason why it's not there for
Same thing for the guys to a lesser degree, but yeah same thing for the guys to a lesser degree
We are like musicians.
Well, anyway, pretty much the perfect list.
If you want to stand in it, there's a accuser.
We didn't die, the accuser got tired of putting trials
so the trials turned out
because we didn't want to go to a court.
I know, it's all crazy.
I mean, maybe I'll, I mean, it's kind of like,
you know, like, I do, what I do like about people,
oh no, your chat's so quiet, oh, where, where, where, where?
It's like, the show is not my chat.
The chat is like,
It's like part of it, you know, it's like this the panel is part of it
There's behind the scenes that are part of it. There's a lot of people that are like, you know
I don't know. I think somebody came in here like accused like oh my god
There's I found another picture of you today. I think I've got a baby photo of you
So do you see is this your baby photo? Oh
I think I've shown pictures of me when I was a little kid before
Well, I mean I was a lot skinnier. I was as a little kid. I hit puberty and I just got super fat
But when I was a little kid, I was like a twig like a twig
Like you I was like you I was like you skinny
But yeah, but I'm still a twig, but yeah, so I think this is so is this you know
Is this your baby photo? I got all during my shit got all fucked up. I find it
happens
That was you as a baby
And it'll happen to you psyche one day. You're gonna get fat and ugly. Just like I am back
One day, but aren't you in your like 20s? I'm already 40. I'm already like, you know, I'm in my thirties
Thank you very much
Yeah, I'm basically a senior citizen. That's you and that's you but that was you then but look at it as an adult
You kind of deflated a little bit, but you are cute. Yeah, I inflated a little bit. I'll give you that
Yeah, you got me. I know it's okay. You got me, dude
Someone see oh my god. Oh my god. Oh
Turn it back on. You're cute
You look like a you look like a some you look like that comic book guy on the Simpsons. It's like, you know
Hey, I'm gonna trade you this for this. Oh shit. I am wearing the same shirt. Oh
See now I can't wear this shirt
Damn, you're right. I can't wear
I don't think I've ever seen him like without a hat. I know he's not wearing his beanie today
He's not wearing his beanie. I'm not wearing my beanie because I'm having sex now
You saw Tommy James was asking for you at that store. Why was he doing that?
He's asking a homeless person if they've seen you. Because yeah, homeless people are the most
Yeah, I mean they can usually figure stuff out, but um
Did you you saw that? Oh, yeah
Yeah, he was looking for his his autistic
What his autistic something's sigment?
Right, that's what he said and then he oh you ever see blackout and you get arrested twice in one night
Twice on one night. Yeah. Yeah, it's not
When you're when you have rich parents that are retarded like he does
It doesn't it's not
There's no like cool factor. There's no like
like
He's just getting bailed out the same day same night. He's getting bailed out like it's not even like oh wow
Like like if you're if you go into prison or jail knowing that you're gonna get out
It's not it's not the same experience
Like he's got to get out of jail free card every time how many DUI's does he have you know how expensive a DUI is?
It's very expensive
thousands and thousands of dollars
Just to throw away because you're being retarded
So, Blackout Andy, this was a few months ago.
He thinks Victoria J, he blames her for this.
I'll play it like a little bit, hopefully you can see it.
This is Blackout Andy.
Victoria J is boring and uninteresting.
Very well, she's having a clip,
but he accuses her of doing it.
She's not in the clip though,
it's just about people who are scared of him.
See it?
I was like, all of this has it's own...
Yeah, I'm a lot of people.
I actually have a Neuralink.
I have a Neuralink and it's actually
um, I'm beaming this video directly on my brain.
It's a true story.
The thoughts that stole my heart seem to fall on my face
In the air with a nail to a cookie
It's so hot that the store's power is fucking shutting out
The place where he is
I was at the store and the power just shut out
They're putting the silver bracelets on the man
Am I too close bro?
Good black guy Andy was in front of me, dude. I would throw him like a fucking basketball
Okay, bye. I would throw him like a retarded basketball
Like a basketball that's retarded at the same time
You got arrested for being gay
Yeah
And that's it justified
Selling
He had a bottle of Patron, but he must have ran out of the oh, is that Trident it's trying the police officer
Well me I got I got myself a rest. I got I got I got arrested, but who was looking to do something?
I wonder hmm just change the title to Victoria Jay got me arrested. She didn't get me arrested. She had a part in it.
She called the cops and told them hey, you know, yes, like they're dropping them. Yes, just like Skibbles.
They're not even they're being dropped like scribbles
Scribbles charges are being dropped. So mine
Okay, that's cool. Bye
If you don't like my face, why the fuck you here faggot nigger?
Hello lawyers. Yep, they were fun. Yeah, they look great on my wrists
Still pretty good actually
Dude this shit was like purple
The shit was fucking purple, bro
Yeah, I'm going on tonight guys, and then I'm done streaming
I'm gonna go out tonight. You're a fan of whoa my last dream tonight guys. Oh
Shit shout out miss Holly
Miss Holly for the 20 with the 20 bro. Fuck
Well, I'm only taking two shots miss Holly. Let's drink this beer. I'm gonna take a dab
And then we need to
Victoria J is a beer
It doesn't matter as long as it's documented Peter Griffin right the butt chin everything cops
I'm going to do anything but as long as the cops don't do anything, but now I have all
this evidence I can say hey look you're fucked with Toya J. Toya J? Yes. Unlock the rest of
um my uh my elderly father he's 81 years old he's been getting um calls and emails from people like
threatening me threatening him saying bad things are gonna happen
you know stuff of that nature fucking cops aren't gonna do anything yep yep yep aunt g that's why
Are the cops gonna drive their fucking police cars fucking to Canada and arrest Victoria J? No
Yeah, I know Brian still
Don't worry about it. Now. I dropped the pizza on the ground, bro. I saw it outside my window, bro
Right if this in the cop car just looking at my pizza on the ground like fuck almost made it home
Is the pizza still detained
It's it's fucking on Victoria
You better never fucking stream again Victoria jay cuz so long
So long as I have breathed in my body
which
Is not right now
As long as I had breathed in my body
I will be on Victoria jay not like a physical way
But as long as I breathed in my body
Not right now
Victoria jay had my parents hate me so much and they don't like me and they keep me across the country
How come I'm here at their house? Huh? Yeah. When's the last time you saw your parents?
Yeah, fuck this fucking one. Victoria J, bitch. Yeah, my dad told me. What the email?
Yeah, you love, you love, you probably all fucking coordinated on discord, huh?
You, Sandman, fucking Victoria J, Sandman, Ron Roller.
Definitely Victoria J and Ron Willow.
I saw him on her panel.
Oh my God.
And like, that's what made me like.
Yeah, but just like, he's so insane.
He was like there with an open bottle
bothering the police when they're arresting someone else
and they kept telling him to go away.
He kept walking over with his camera, filming them.
And so they eventually got hired of and arrested him.
I mean, it's like, and then he's saying
Sam Mann and Victoria J are in a discord.
plotting to call the police I don't know I just think it's kind of funny like
the delusion my blinds up because I was like what the fuck I think this is
terrible use of the limited time yeah no they definitely coordinated it get it
rested against definitely some kind of coordinated attack with one roller look
at the toy a jay probably BG percol shows up probably BG they probably called
They probably they all probably called so much like the cops were like, oh, well, we can't really do anything
Really no he's not doing anything
They were driving by dude. They were watching me
Remember when I was sitting there by the pizza place like drinking a beer was like up the cops are there up up and I zoomed in
Yeah
Cop probably saw it they were like fuck this guy. Yep, they called the cops exactly yep
They all fucking coordinated it like thank you. If you were if you were to like pop up in heaven
Would you be happy with how you spend the last five years
Letting you on the show one too many times, but you know what
Then that's that's and that's your life life long like like huh. That's it
I need to kind of get my story straight watch that can't be like
Fucking spoking out. Oh like acting a fool
We're doing
I'm waiting on here so the cops don't like
You know look inside the house
Not that I have anything illegal in the house, but
Like cops see like a dab rig and
Like they start to ask questions
Put away the dab rig. I mean, it's like not that
Is that this domain intensifying? Oh, this is perfect weather the cops are here. Look at the cops here
I mean what you want some big cops, right? Cops in here guys. This will be fun. Oh, it's a woman cop. Awesome
Yeah, great
Yeah, a woman cop. We need a a female officer. Yeah, women should be police officers equal rights
Yeah, recently my dad has been receiving these like calls
And emails from people online like I live stream, which is what I'm doing right now
And they were like like psychotic like just insane people that you know, like as there are in the world
But they've just like been like harassing my dad, and he's like 80 years old, and he doesn't go online.
I mean, he knows I livestream, he knows I do this, but he doesn't have any interaction with the people online,
and they've just been like targeting him.
Like I think I have an idea who it is because like this person like called him and like left him a voicemail
Was like your son blah blah blah this and that online blah blah
And this is all just like online like internet stuff like this is nothing serious like this is just you know over like stupid things
And bothering my dad over this
I mean I can I can go get him if you want to I mean
It's I mean like it's people like online doing this like it's the harassing like elderly people my dad like I can go get him
Hold on
Well, why didn't I come here on Sunday? Yeah, don't hit me
Don't hit me you fuck. Was that a cop in that car?
That was a police officer in that fucking car
Fucking faggot cops
Yeah, OPD can't suck my fucking fat dick
You can suck my fat
Fucking glizzy sized fucking cock
Fucking Orlando Police Department
Back at the same exact pace.
Take Gustav Elgar.
With these fucking Fent heads here.
I'm not, and tell them you're a Scorpio.
I'm not a Scorpio.
I'm a Libra.
This is so much better.
There's no hops around.
There's like way less monkeys.
Oh, look.
There's no monkeys around.
All the monkeys stay home, I guess.
I don't know, bro.
Well, I played with them.
Yeah, this is where I was last time, bro.
Look at my Bud Light, look at bro, my Bud Light cap is still on the ground. Let's go from like Friday or whatever
Bud Light Lime is disgusting. Let's try to be a guys
Hey, you guys make sure you call OPD on me
Fucking all my haters
Go get me a vested bro
Get me a vested whoa
You guys want their number?
Want to call the Orlando police here you go guys
Call them up. Tell them, you know, whatever you want. Tell them whatever lies you want to tell them.
That's fine. They'll just be content for me.
Can I Apple pay you now, bud?
Hot mess just says, Mace is ready.
Yep, Mace is ready, yeah.
What was happening here at your time?
Oh, yeah, she was, bro. That was fucking cool.
Yeah, my mace is right here. Hold on Nanna says happy birthday. Thank you. No, no psyche. Have you ever been nice?
Mace is fun for you sends her. I'm gonna fucking motor Victoria as well
Especially when you're not
Little saber. Hey, I got from Walmart
Want to get suede?
Now I got the mace, I got the jogger fogger, I got the nigger knocker, I got the strap, I got the glock, I got the jogger fogger and I got the nigger knocker, I got the jogger fogger and I got the nigger knocker, I got the jogger fogger and I got the nigger knocker, I got the jogger fogger and I got the nigger knocker, I got the jogger fogger and I got the nigger knocker, I got the jogger fogger and I got the nigger knocker, I got the jogger fogger and I got the nigger knocker, I got the jogger fogger and I got the jogger fogger and I got the nigger knocker, I got the jogger fogger and I got the jogger fogger and I got the nigger knocker, I got the jogger fogger and I got the jogger fogger and I got the
Get ready you fucking faggots. This is my last live stream. I mean I'm lost. I well, this is my last
Toria
I want to
Lots of last dream so bad
All right
Hey, how are you?
Yo, it's hot, bro!
All right, don't pour it out.
Oh, it's hot, bro.
All right, do me a favor, put your hands on your back.
For what?
Put your hands on your back.
Am I getting invested again?
For what?
Mike's selling to a sales manager.
And you're going to park up there.
Park up there.
I don't understand.
You have to try to put alcohol inside of the park.
Do we do the same?
I'm getting invested, guys.
Again?
Yes, sir.
What am I getting?
Oh, man.
Don't sway me, bro.
Yes, I just told you.
OK.
Don't sway me. Whoa, which is actually considerate. I'm sorry
Can you please end that how do you do it a little and yes, yes, sir
Don't sway me whoa
Look there. I am see like I get big good views on this
He has viewers now
So I see some kick streamers fighting in Florida. It's only five minutes, but why are they doing that?
There's no exclamation or anything, but it's just on trip kick.
Oh, yeah?
Let me stabilize my sphincter.
Yeah, we got some bitty oil here.
I should get some bitty oil.
All right.
If he does something to me, I'll still got him, bro.
You ain't got him, bro!
Look at your fucking body!
You don't work out!
I don't need no purpose, bro.
What's up?
I bet that's gonna work out. It's obvious you're not fighting a person.
I've trained. I'm a real man and a main fighter.
I'm not just a real man.
I'm not reacting hard.
You are reacting hard.
Why are you switching? Sorry.
I thought you said you were from the streets.
Why are you switching?
That's my homie.
And you're switching with Mr. Brown.
They're all snitching.
That's why your skin is shivered.
I'm gonna tear you on this action, man.
Trying to have legal bullshit.
Waiting for him to have asses.
Y'all can't. Y'all can't.
You gave your home for me, but you're home for me.
I'd like to kill you.
Yo shit, bro. Yo shit.
Well, if you have your extra care,
I'd like to kill you.
Please play at the last stage in the back of the area.
Oh, two.
I don't know.
Please continue scanning.
Bang, bang, boom, boom.
I don't know.
Please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please
Not every racist person is loud, but every loud person is racist.
What do you think about this, like he?
What does it taste like?
Who got it?
Let's get out of here before 12, let's get out of here before 12, let's get out of here
I don't have more fucking pillows.
Bro, how do you have pillows?
I don't have pillows.
That guy is fucking weird.
This guy is weird.
I don't have pillows.
You're weird.
Yo Psyche, when are we gonna have sex?
Isn't it recording in my own live stream?
I'm horny.
Where are you? How far away are you?
Like 800 miles away.
That's too far
Okay, Rose until the investigation did you hear that?
The federal aviation authority made they released a video
kind of hinting
That we're gonna do
Supersonic travel again
You know, it's like super like it's gonna be planes that like instead of it taking 12 hours to get to LA
It'll be like a three-hour flight.
He said, can I borrow $20?
What was that?
Never mind.
Can I borrow $20?
Do you want to borrow $20?
Why?
Well, because I can do cool stuff today.
You didn't get what?
I can get drunk.
I can eat.
I can get cigars.
And you don't have your own money?
Not today.
Yeah, you will
I
Don't know if I can I'll give you money. I could give you a loan. Okay
That has interest on it
Okay
Let's do that. We would be the bank is basically like a payday loan. It's gonna be a very high interest rate
Well, how about if I pay it really back really fast? How about that?
Yes, exactly. But also the insurance rate of the APY is going to kick in.
It's going to compound by the minute. Usually these things
He's paid day long as a very sensitive financial instruments. Okay. Okay, and Rose I just like I'm just like I'm on it
Cuz it's like it rose under a lot of stress
And I don't want Rose being attacked right now by like by saying oh, she's she's a mod in his jet
Like I think that it's over. I miss you know like, you know
Just wait for a minute and like give her a break from it, you know, it's like stressful. It is stressful
And like, you know, some people in here will be picked up saying you can't show weakness.
I have to do like troll training army and stuff.
And I need stuff to learn to because, you know, it's like hard because it's like
when your whole audience is trolls almost, it's like, you know, it's hard.
So you have to do anti-racism training, like the ones they do at liberal arts universities.
Okay.
Then you will be fixed.
and cured of this illness that you have.
I want to do something so humiliating
that I am motivated to start making my own money,
which is like, I'm asking SIG for a loan.
Fine.
He needs a small loan of a million dollars.
Yeah.
Just send a million dollars, SIG, all of them,
and then you can do that, yeah, send it.
If you give me an actual good reason, I will do it.
Okay, well, I'll do IRL to the pier, I will...
There's a lot of good use of million dollars.
Oh, million dollars?
Well, I think even for like $20, over a million dollars,
I would be like your pool boy,
and I would just have a show around your pool,
and it's like, and then you could come in
and like do your show whenever you want,
and it's like, and you could,
and I'd like kind of like just treat you like a king.
I still not a good use of money over a million dollars.
I mean, no, no, I mean, it's been like $10,000 doing that
and you'd be paying me.
Yeah, that's more like, that's more like 300 maybe.
That's more like buy, that's more like my,
sorry, I'm just getting into my fantasies.
Oh, three, okay.
That's more like, that's more like you paying me
three to $500.
Okay, well let's, okay, so what's the low I'm gonna be?
Just give me a number.
The lowest bid?
Go ahead and see me alone and then I'll see if I'll tell you if it's like I'll take the loan and what's collateral?
Um, my collateral is, um, I have an apartment, I have like thousands of dollars of books.
I have, you know, I'm, I'm, I'm actually on live so you can like always confront me
and like, and then you'll be able to, you'd be able to say, oh, I ripped you off if I ripped
you off.
I mean, so it's like, there's embarrassment.
I'll send you my like, um, my driver's license, like, and I'll have to, uh, mount
that.
What if you put an air tag inside of your skin?
Okay.
It's not a surgery. You just have to you're just going to do it yourself
Can I put it in between my butt cheeks?
No, it's gonna you have to implant it into your skin. Can I put it and I'm planted into my butt?
No, no, that's not that won't mean that's necessary
But don't you want to always know where I am say are you in an air tag me you want to tag me like a
cattle
Yeah, and then and then I'm gonna brand you
I'm gonna brand you with a hot iron red hot iron. The red iron. Is it gonna have your
Can please look like this. I want it to be like this
And it's gonna be it's gonna be it's gonna be like the one that Van Margera got except it's the shape of my cock to scale
Can I get that tattoo to my butt right there and detailed? Yeah, but it's gonna be a brand
Oh, we're gonna bring it to the blob fish brand. It's gonna be it's like a ultra detailed brand like you see all the veins and everything ultra detail
To Sam to scale to scale. Why do you want to like see see my butt so bad?
By you want to put it or you want to put it on my butt, right?
The problem the problem with it going inside is that if it goes inside you lose signal
Okay, well, you know, I'd say I think I just rather starve never mind
Yeah, so you need $20 or you were starved to death
Well, then I could also drink and then I could like also smoke. You're gonna trick
drink
That's it. That's extreme. I'm not gonna trick
I want to give my enemies ammunition right now
I'm sorry
Psyche likes being gay and weird
I do. It's just how I am. Brandon rejected me.
You're just gay, psyche. It's okay.
Hey, say, Brandon rejected me.
Wow. This is really one of the worst things
that could possibly happen to a person.
I didn't see the light, and he saw everything.
He didn't care then. I rejected him.
Not like he said, oh, yeah, Brandon's bad one day.
and he has child mods.
Okay, well, that's all you got.
Okay, well, I feel rejected again.
Again, another rejection, Sig.
I mean, it's like, how many more can I take?
How many more, how much more, how much more rejection
can I take if I'm just gonna be thrown in the dumpster?
The more the better.
I mean I need like more rejections. You need to get you need to get rejected more so that you develop a thicker skin
That my psyche haters I think that's where the money is now in the haters club. I think like
It's very unfortunate. Yes, there's this just seems to be a function of life
where there's more money there's more money in destruction there's more there's so much there's so much money in the defense industry like you can make so much money figuring out different ways to kill someone
and chop their body up into pieces like literally there's so much money billions trillions of dollars it's crazy
It's really crazy, but, you know, you want to solve cancer, there's no money in that.
There's no fucking money in that.
Shout out to, shout out to Psyche because he's a gay guy, and so because he's a gay
guy, he supports this system.
that's what everybody
I mean it's like
now you support this gay system
this is a gay system that's being upheld
by ditty Epstein
well I mean it works works
of the world
these are the ditty Epstein people
no no they're all in jail are dead
I mean come on look at the
oh you really believe that
All of them really you think so well, that's two people did he and I
Said they're in jail are dead and they're both in jail are dead probably or they did he's alive, right?
I don't know. Do you want to see a cool video? I'm just allowed to play it because
Monetize
Well, you want to see it?
Okay, bro. You're really smoked up. That's what you think
You're really like you're like white pill. Would you just say to me?
You're white pill
Don't call me white a white pill. Okay. Hold on. You think you you're really white pill. You think everything is safe
Nothing is say everything is dangerous and horrible. You think that everything is safe psyche. I'm yelling at me sir
Delusional psyche. Well, maybe maybe but at least I have them, but okay, okay?
He's in Alice and Wonderland in a mod hybrid
You're watching I'm watching the part where psyche removes his clothes back
That's the part that I like the most
Psyche I've been working all day
I'm horny
Fuck my dick. I'm so horny. I would fuck a cereal box right now
I'll put my dick into Tony the Tigers
was literally about to say that. Let's see if she has the right stuff. Do you have music
prepared? I mean, it's weird. I mean, it's all weird, but it's like, it's not like anything.
It's like, uh, like, you're the weird one. This video is really good. Yo, Yo, thank you.
Did you hear you know who was on pikers? We'll watch it later. We'll do it tonight or something.
low key this guy this guy is a whole nutcase and then you know his uncle
chunky yogurt what's his name? Chanky Uygurt? Chanky Uygurt? Chunky Uygurt?
Just look it up just type it into YouTube search what's that?
I want to watch a free video of Brandon, and they're kind of like,
full set on off.
Yo, thank you full screen you.
I'm having sex.
Frankie, you don't have sex like I do.
Beautiful safe.
This is a healthy white affluent neighborhood
with all the white women outside.
When does he think, uh...
Are you here with the ambassadors?
Yes, I am.
I'm a diplomat, actually.
Are those Mexican flags you have on your windshield?
No, that's the Italian flag.
Italian flag?
Why are you re-representing your race?
Because I'm Christopher Columbus's great, great, great,
great grandfather.
That's some kind of Freemasonic reference.
OK, never mind, never mind, never mind.
OK, OK.
What does your cat want?
She wants to say hi to you.
She's like,
I'm the only pussy exactly I ever talked to.
That's what I say.
Okay.
Oh yeah.
That's what psyche says.
Yeah.
Okay.
Send them to Discord.
So, I mean, Brandon,
like see,
and then everyone can come to their own conclusions
about this tape, I guess.
Like, and you can tell me what you think.
Cause I really like,
I watched it and it's like,
I mean there's like, you know, there's like a lot a lot a lot a lot a lot of posts about it
So I mean I think I'm not gonna go through this like I don't want to go through this this all day and stuff
What is this gamble? I mean, it's like I'm getting too much
Posts, huh? I mean, I think there's so many. What do I play? I play
These are like so there's so many. I don't know
It's like he just kicked himself out.
Okay, I'm sorry.
I'm not gonna play that, you know why?
Because that's what got Brandon kicked off of YouTube.
Played that clip of Gamble, like, you know,
showing his ass or whatever.
I don't care.
I mean, it's like, I don't want to like make this,
I don't want to get involved and stuff.
I mean, this is like, this is all ridiculous.
Okay, I'm gonna play a music video.
Or, but I'll play it to your,
Driving, okay. I'll put you on full screen. I'll play some songs. Okay. I'm gonna play my math shard
Can I play with you? Can I play with your wiener when I put this on?
I'll put out the big screens and all can see. I'm just kidding. That's a just a joke. We're going to Connecticut
We are
Yes, you and me and chat and tricks. Yeah, it's gonna go tricks is there's you oh my gosh
This is like heaven. It's like heaven
Okay, so this is called André Chickatillo, but I'll put you on full screen during it, okay, hold on a second.
Wait, you can play it, go ahead and play your music video or whatever, your LGBTQ homosexual shit.
Okay.
No, you like to watch gay dudes dancing, and I respect that.
Okay, let's check it out.
I respect that Psyche wants to watch gay dudes have anal sex.
I'll let you know when the sign pops up and then you can full-screen me.
I wanna kill people.
That's just a good band because there are other songs about actuals.
So you wanna chop people up into pieces and turn them into chicken nuggets.
No, that's your fantasy. You're projecting onto me.
That's what you're saying you want to do. No, I don't know. I just I didn't ever I know I like that band that
That was like the first time I saw that video. I just want to play this a video from them
And they're always pretty good. Hey, Mr. Extendo. Do you want to talk to SIGS? SIGS up here with it with me
I'm driving my car without a seatbelt. Yeah, I'm doing actual I have like, you know doing IRL on the show right?
I don't know. Hopefully my show didn't go down just like yeah psyched the bike
Yeah, I mean, it's like, you know, the Harry's on Seekers
I was like, can we build a bicycle for two but then Harry's bikes never have a never have a seat
They just have a big dildo that he insert some so far. I believe that too. Yeah, it's true
And you guys just share it
Rose if you don't be here like like just I mean I mean you're going
That's the chat Rose. I don't I think you the mod went to your head a little bit
Oh, so just let the other Mods take care of stuff. No, they're like out for me
Mr. Extendo great in the chat. Hello everybody see look at so see where are you writing to are you hiding the body somewhere?
Yeah, there's this Connecticut sign
They were in the Connecticut. Are you gonna meet Martha Stewart and a snoop dog as you see the sign?
I just passed it. It said welcome to Connecticut. I saw that but are you bet you know Martha Stewart lives in Connecticut?
I think I'm gonna go over there. Yeah, I'm gonna go fuck her
Right you do that
Yeah, it's gonna be great
Totally worth the trip
But just for like you would like what but you would expect like we didn't return right?
I mean that I think with Martha Stewart. That's assumed. No
Like we don't have to talk about that
You gotta talk everybody smoking
Everybody's shooting math to really where is it? I don't it's never around me
Well, that's because you don't know how to hang around real meth tutors.
Oh, do I have people to shoot it?
Meth tutors, yeah, bro.
It's disgusting.
I want the meth shards in my veins.
I want the math chart slicing up my veins all over my heart.
Oh my God, sounds like a, hey, Electra, oh my God, I need to, oh my God, Electra, I've been looking for you, I'm so sorry.
Everything's been going bad, I'm going to have to, I'm going to be modding you right now, I'm so sorry.
Everything's all bad, like, come up please if you can.
Please come up and then maybe mr. Extendo like mr. Extendo. It's Joker
She found out that her boyfriend only wants her for sex after bang
Hey
You'd be nice to Electra
I
Would be nice to her even though she's not nice to me bang
So Rose likes Joker everything is bad here. She you get it
I don't know, Electra, but I do want to show Electra what says in the codex about her, but I want to see what it says about Sig today too, because on my codex I just re-enriched everything, so it should have a deeper understanding of all the lore, and now everything is always added, so I'll see what it says about Electra, and about, oh, let me see if I can log in, yes, I'm logged in, okay, where's my oracle? Oracle, oracle, oracle.
Okay, actually, I can show you this here's a start here pain gay oracle
Everybody can like also go ask a few free questions to the Oracle you without even having to sign up or anything
But here
You can ask about anybody on the show and like anything about the show. So there's the link to it
That's like a start here page, but you can go to the side. You see where it says Oracle. I'm gonna click on that
I'm gonna share the screen. Hold on. Okay. It's pretty cool
And if I type in Electra, DJElectra, let's see what it says.
Okay, so here's the Oracle.
Okay, and so here it says, you know, consult the Oracle.
So you just type DJElectra.
Okay.
I've probably shown her before,
but let's see it, sometimes it changes and stuff.
Okay, so it says.
It says, DJ Electra is the etheric artisan embedded in the archives substrate.
She does not perform, she builds, she composes the signature intro music that opens every
transmission authored to the visual manifesto that frames the panel burst and is gifted
equipment, earbuds, headphones that solve critical audio infrastructure problems.
whose functional importance exceeds her visibility.
He operates as a creative infrastructure figure,
moving beyond performance into direct material and sonic support.
The archive recognizes her as a figure of genuine care.
Prairie Page collaborated with her to gift gaming earbuds to Psyche,
and she appears consistently in moments of community steadiness.
She anchors the show's aesthetic without demanding center stage.
creative and committed, a presence felt through sound and gift, not spectacle.
Isn't that beautiful? Let's see what it says about Sig. Have you ever seen it, Sig?
No. It says, okay, I'm typing in Sig and it says Sig. Okay.
He says, SIG enters the archive as the exiled betrayer,
a figure rendered entirely through condemnation,
never through presence.
He used images of another to weaponize obscenity
in Psyche's broadcast space,
triggering the command that births the Lord itself.
Do not ever, ever, ever show me your vagina again, SIG.
The prior relationship.
saying is donation recipient positioned as supplicant amplifies like transgression into betrayal
Psycule's documentation of a presidential assassination threat video allegedly produced by
That's weird. I forget who kept saying that when somebody kept
Oh my god, it's buddy. Oh my god.
This is the funniest thing I've ever read.
It says, the prior relationship, okay,
so I don't know what the donation was,
but it says, I don't know if I have this material.
I have to look into my archives,
I have these vaults in the back,
but it says, I hold documentation
of a presidential assassination threat
that you have produced, held in reserve,
saying this in the archive is not as a warning,
but as a warning, a name threshold,
once crossed, cannot be uncrossed.
The vulgarity that named him is the will,
Wall between belonging and exile. Well, I guess you're just the wall now because you're half in and half out sick
I mean, it's crazy. I mean a happy Canada day by the way. Hey
Did everyone see what?
You know the thing that a thing that is and you know, we heard that Hugh went to the beach and so thing that is Apollo
And me decided we were gonna have our own beach party to hear about that thing
No
there
Say
Yeah, do you see us?
How do we look
You can't see me. Oh, I'm gonna add you to that. I'm gonna add you to it. Hold on so well. Oh, yeah, you're Mexico, right?
Okay, yeah, we have a now we have a fourth, okay
So yeah, so I you know I can make it I can like I can like you know conjure up something with within a few seconds actually
So I would say okay
So tell me about your day. I'm sick. I'm what else are you doing in Connecticut besides Martha Stewart?
primary
Objective
This one
Are you missing or did you see it what would you show you should you didn't show your penis did you?
No, there's a river called my anus. Oh
my anus
There's literally called M-I-A-U-N-U-S.
Okay, well, I see it. Okay, so, say, I did my best with this.
I don't think I got it, like, perfect, okay?
Um, thing that is, you're still in the beach crew, okay?
What do you think, guys?
Still in the what?
Oh, my gosh, Rose is here.
She's gonna prove once and for all that she's an adult guys. This will be really embarrassing if this is a child
And guys a DJ electric you get up here immediately before we enter Gary interrogate Rose
please
DJ like I need you here because I need like you know, I need to make sure like I'm doing everything right because
What is that picture first of all Rose? I mean, it's like is that a
That the tiles pitch. I mean, I'm really confused about this. I just don't it might be Brandon Q putting up things
It's probably Brandon. Is that you rose coming up in the back?
Roses are roses are at roses are ed
Okay, well, I don't know say you're
Say why are you black? I said I'm only black from the waist down bang
Why is a thing is you stole my baby? It looks like I it looks like it looks like that. It's a guy
It's untrackable. It looks like untrackable
Okay, I'm gonna put up a banner. Hold on. I'm gonna put up a banner and make sure that it's the right person
I'm gonna make sure that Rose is an adult and the will wills will know by her voice for sure. Okay, Rose
Rose
Rose are you there?
Oh, hold on. I took them off. It wasn't a black eye. Hello? Rose. Rose. I hear something.
Do you hear something? Rose, are you there? Hello? I can't hear her. Did you hear that
sound? No. I don't know. Rose, you have to fix your microphone and come back later. I'm
so sorry. How's she now? Yeah, let's get back to the good stuff. Yeah, she left. We're
Perfect. I'm really getting into the summertime mood, aren't you? See? It was you that was making
that noise. There's not even a Draco pistol, whatever your name is. Get out of here. Come
back later. Okay guys, this is just, I'm just going to show you how things can become misunderstood.
So Brandon said that he had a picture of clumsy, right? Like of clumsy.
And so, he shared this picture, he said it was from a gay escort website, okay?
And so, we all posted this, or we were all posting it and saying,
oh, here's Clonesies.
And I didn't know if it was him, but there's a picture right there.
And then I like searched and I found this is totally out of context, because look,
it's actually a video of a guy just blowing up a balloon, or bubble gum or something like that.
So it's like something like totally normal and it's taken way out of context
You know
So that's a lesson for us because it's in terms of picture like when you watch the video
It makes a bunch more sense what's happening in the picture because you would think oh
He has one of those gag balls in his mouth and he looks like he has no eyebrows and stuff
This is a man with alopecia. Okay. He doesn't have those tattoos that clumsy has actually this is a woman
You know, it's a woman with alopecia and um, but it but she was just blowing up a balloon
So don't be so quick to judge people.
It's not some kind of gay sex thing.
Why would you say something such as this thing?
Oh, and here's how I talk to Alexandra.
I talk like this because I have a gay accent
and this is how I talk because I'm so precious.
I've never even heard that kind of voice
come out of anybody, but I know, or myself.
He says her.
Oh, I talk like this.
What am I, what am I, Vivian Lay from Gone with the Wind?
I don't have a Southern accent.
I don't talk like a, like some Richard Simmons, you know,
archetype.
Oh, oh.
It's the worst imitation of me I've ever seen.
Oh, if I do say so myself.
I'm gonna start doing a bad imitation of you, Alex.
Good morning.
Good afternoon.
Good evening.
Actually, there's no better imitation of her than.
Stoner scribe, and I'm not gonna play the Brandon one again. I think I think I got under skin a little bit
So I'll save that for later, but I will
be playing a
Depth a different stoner scribe
But I think it's brilliant
And I'm even mentioned it even so I mean I can play it because I mentioned it
I'm like literally the heat like my whatever is my name is the set in it. So you'll see are you ready to see it? Okay?
If you like what you see today, consider donating down below. Every little bit helps the channel grow. Thank you so much. Enjoy
Hi, Sonic me
Everyone good morning. Good. Wow. What's this thing? Whatever time it is
This is our ever in this fast world. You may who is this way? Pause it real quick. Oh
Your mic isn't picking up very good. Are you far away from it? No? Um, yeah
Okay. You're like, I'm just chilling on the couch.
I'm having a rough day.
I think we should get you in for a haircut today.
What do you think about that?
That might be something good and uplifting.
If someone could help sponsor me,
I would be happy to get a haircut.
I would do it on the air, I would like, you know.
That'd be fun.
Yeah, it would be fun.
Everybody, would everyone like me to get a haircut?
I can even just use my clipper.
I'll shave my head.
How much should I shave?
No, no, no, no, no, don't shave it.
Just get like a nice, close cut, like not too short.
Cause you have such nice full hair
and you have a good head of hair for a man your age,
like you're so blessed.
Most men wish they could have that much hair.
I know, but you just need to clean it up a little bit and I think you in maybe shave a little bit shave that neck
Come on psyche. I'm just not been feeling it right now
It's terrible.
Well, it's like, everyone's been dumping me
like left and right.
You know, like Jamie's Cowboys was like left me.
You know, Alexandra left me.
My friend, Joni left me.
Then like-
Did they say that there was a reason
or are they just busy doing other stuff?
It just blew up on me over nothing.
Each one of them, it was like, there's nothing.
Like they just blew up at me.
for like, making my own decisions and stuff like that.
I mean, if they don't like my decisions or whatever
or like, what were my actions or what I've done?
I mean, I don't know if I, my actions weren't even bad.
I didn't mean, the thing is like,
oh, you know what you did.
That's what they say.
Or you're, or you're disgusting.
You're, you're disgusted, like all this kind of stuff.
And it's like-
Aw.
What happened?
I don't understand.
I haven't been around.
I'm sorry.
I've been dealing with a bunch of stuff in real life.
I haven't been online like pretty much at all.
Took my channel down for a week even you did yeah, I mean I mean the only way I can do it as I get there's like
This is the best way I can explain it is like we're showing you something like it's like real quick
and you can comment during it, but it's like this is like there's like something really crazy stuff has happened and
I mean it's like I can show and it's all
Uh rumors and not verified right and no one has receipts right welcome back to explain it so
On that perfectly shows how fast digital drama can snowball into real-world paranoia, but why keep
Unpacking a sprawling 49 minute live stream broadcast by alexander melody mayors titled irl news time live
And let me tell you this broadcast is an absolute whirlwind. It's packed with severe allegations messy interpersonal drama and some incredibly serious
challenges. So to make sense of all this chaos without getting completely lost in
the noise, we're gonna stick strictly to what was stated in the broadcast. We'll
be mapping out the claims, the targets, and specifically those intense slander
allegations directed at a creator named Psyche. Okay, let's dive into this. Right
out of the gate, you need to understand just how incredibly high stakes and,
frankly, combative this broadcast gets. Alexandra doesn't just brush off her
critics. She openly dares them to act against her.
Listen to this quote from her stream pick up the phone get on the phone with these people and let them know that
I'm currently in Scottsdale, Arizona turn me in. I mean wow
That's not a passive disagreement, right? That is a positive for a direct confrontation being broadcast live to the internet
So think of this next I don't I'm confused. What is this? What is this? I'm confused
This is an this is like an analysis of one of her shows and okay, so she said she was in Scottsdale, Arizona
Yeah, well because she has to turn herself in
What did she do? She's a warrant there like it was really for what first first slander
I think or something like that, but it was an it was because she didn't show up in court
So they weren't for her arrest for someone took her to court for slander. Okay, was it Lee?
I mean, it's a complicated thing, but that's what she started out. Who was it?
Amber, Amber had a, had a charges over in Arizona,
but it was like, she never, so then she was,
said she was in Yuma, Arizona at this certain address
and gave her a dress out and everything on the air
and told her full name and stuff.
And like, dare you call the police on me?
I mean, the cops really aren't looking to go pick people
up on warrants like that.
They really don't care.
You'll only get picked up on a warrant like that
if you get pulled over, say, and you have that warrant.
They might take you in.
They probably won't.
They don't have fucking time for this bullshit.
Stupid online fucking fights that people are having are you kidding me? I don't have time for this shit
There's too much real crime going on stop with your online bullshit people. Come on
Yeah, but let's not see but it starts with something like that
But look how I just want to show you how to escalate. I can't even describe it perfectly
I think this would this describes it perfectly and I think that uh, just it's just like a few more minutes
Like I swear, it's like everything's like a minute long, but it's like it's pretty it's string board
It's gonna help us keep track. We'll quickly look at one public challenge
She issues to the alleged drug ring three her network of targets and for the allegations against psyche
Let's keep moving
All right, kicking things off with section one, the public challenge and her defensive posture.
So, Alexandra starts this broadcast leaning all the way in to a deeply aggressive defensive stance.
During the stream, she repeatedly dares her audience and her critics to take actual legal action.
She literally looks at the camera and asks, so who's going to turn me in?
Who's going to turn me in? This is where I am. Anyone want to meet for breakfast?
It is such a fascinating rhetorical strategy.
She's dealing with all these community accusations and
her responses to basically throw the gauntlet down.
She's demanding that if anyone has proof,
they need to take it straight to the authorities.
Now, what's really interesting about this is how she
actually weaponizes her own physical location.
She uses it like a shield.
She literally puts her specific Scottsdale,
Arizona address out there for everyone to see.
She even drops the direct contact info for
both the Yuma and Scottsdale police departments.
She claims that specific public figures
have court paperwork ready to get her arrested.
So by putting all her info out there,
she's framing the act of calling the cops
as the ultimate test.
She's implying, hey, if you don't call the police on me
right now, your claims must be totally fake.
Moving on to section two, the alleged drug ring
and how she completely shifts the narrative.
And this brilliantly illustrates the massive pivot she pulls in the livestream.
People in the community had been throwing around some extremely heavy labels,
specifically calling certain individuals pedophiles.
But Alexandra? She counters with something entirely different.
She claims that whole label is just a coordinated smokescreen.
The real truth according to her is if these individuals are actually running an organized illegal drug distribution ring.
She's basically saying that those disturbing community accusations
are just a cover up for a massive network of dealers.
OK, so who exactly does she claim is in this illicit network?
Well, she points her finger at a very specific group of people.
She names Brandon Quintana, Thomas Oaks,
who she calls Junkie James, Carl, J-Dog, Clumsy, Sandman,
and Bita Mustafavi.
And she is absolutely adamant here.
Psyche, can I say something real quick?
They are just addicts, they're active distributors in the drug trade.
Now remember we are just can you pause it? Okay, so I don't understand why
Alexandra is hanging out with these people or if you are or not
I don't understand, but how about just not hanging out with crappy people like this
But she's she was about to make up like we were just getting along for three months
We made up for month for months and then she just turned on me in a day
And it's like but but you know that pattern exists and you know, it's happened before
So how about just not hanging out with people like that anymore?
I know who don't uplift you and who don't uplift your content and who don't support your channel
Don't who don't support you and who don't stick by you win
You know if you had contacted me, I would have been right over here
I hadn't heard from you and in a while and honestly, you know, I wasn't online
But still I never got mad at you for anything or left, but I'm just saying like
How about finding people that you can relate to and make content with about something good and and
Productive I want to but now it's just gone to the point where people just hate me and it's like, you know because of like
Brandon thing and then and like because like she took up his cause kind of and then it's like
And then I had a kind of falling out with him
but he was still friends with her and then but then he betrayed her and so she's like mad at me for not like
Warning her about like how he was gonna do that or something and then she's turned on me again
And it's like it's like musical chairs and it's like then she goes to like now
She's back on good times and and and talking to Q and stuff it and it just changes her
her mind like
All I can say is stay away from her stay away from all these people that this video is talking about I
Mean change the name on your channel get a new channel. I don't care what you have to do
Start over if that's what you know is gonna get you out of this loop of negativity and
Horrible people. No, but it's like a spider web and it's like what I feel like, you know, hopefully maybe you can easily start over
I know I know I've been trying but the cold codex is awesome. Isn't that cool that like how it does it and stuff like there
What's it called the cold codex like you know that our code codex cold codex dot me
have a look at that. Yeah, that's my website. It's it's archived every single episode. You're
on there. So it's like everyone's on there on the show. You can ask the oracles and free questions
and stuff. But it's also a way to support the show if anyone wants to like, you know, be cool.
You know, I never really liked the cult take angle, but that was just me. I get it. Like,
you like it. And it's what you're doing. And I understand. And it's, it's what you're doing.
Yeah, I mean it's people because people think it's seriously it's supposed to be like kind of an ironic thing or like it was kind of like a more
Of course
Arpegin thing too because like also like it was like kind of like one start
I always like the idea of like and like the kind of like aesthetic in the comedy aesthetic of it and stuff
but
You know jamie would always say oh, you know change the name
I'm like well, they can't change the name at this point like I was like, you know
She's like I'll just change it to something and so I do have like other channels, you know, but a couple other channels, but it's like, you know
You know, they're small and they're slow-growing. Yeah, it's gonna be like that for a while
I put out when I took my channel down for a week psyche
I had people talking stuff on me and saying things and I didn't like it
And so I just took my channel down for a week. I started a new channel put up one short
and got like 100 subscribers and over 80,000 views
on one short.
Wow, that's awesome.
So I mean, you can start from nothing
and build yourself up again.
You did it the first time.
You did it another time when your channel got taken down,
so.
Yep, you've helped me.
Hey, Thig.
Look how good Thig looks.
What's up?
You're out of the house.
That's good to see.
Hello
Is he muted or something? I thought that's half a heart. Yo. Oh, I hear you know I'm having sex right now
No, you're in a car driving right now
I'm having sex while I'm driving. No, you're not but that's okay. That's funny. Ha ha
It's not a joke
That's the thing. It's not even a joke
We're having sex with it. It's funny though
Really call the police it's funny. It's not supposed to be fun. It's 300 glow in the in the truck with you as your seat
300 glow is
my
Lady of the night
Okay, he's gay
300 glow prostitutes himself for E and J bottles
Do you have food in your are you delivering food to people or are you do you eat it before you get to their house?
And then they have to complain about you. I'm delivering
Bitcoins
What oh my god, what why is he so strange? Okay? I gotta go. It's like he I don't buy into this bullshit
Shay I'm taking him off taking him off. Wait a second. Wait taking him off get out of here sick out pervert
Where's he's not making any sense. What what is that? It's just disgusting. Why keep someone? It's just gross like ew
Nobody wants to think about him having sex especially not while driving and like
I was looking at spots up by you to move I mean not just because you're there, but like I'm looking all over but
Find someplace so fun. Don't be so cool if you find some place where we can see like with help with that with binoculars to each other
When that was that would be cool. We could just be we could even if we're just neighbors or something that'd be pretty fun
Like he is so cool. You guys like
He gets a bad name online like and who cares cuz those people don't know you in real life. They don't know anything about you
It's really like put a lot out because now it's like, you know, it's like, oh now I'm being put in a because I won't play any
More that video, but it's like basically it goes into like how there's an extortion ring and now I'm ready to store now
It's out of that get away from all that
Yeah, run run run far away from anything like that. You don't need that in your life
It's not real life either by the way, you know that
None of that is real
Those are people talking words out their mouth that are not true
And you need to separate that from real life
You got sucked into this false reality on YouTube and it's all false
Yeah, it's like a movie but it's like that's a thing about control that you have gotten sucked into it
I will separate yourself. Please. That's not who you are
We were all we all are all you know, I I left I I stopped dealing with those
I don't even they don't come up on my
Algorithm, nothing.
It's nothing involved.
I don't involve myself with low vibration people like that.
I know.
But you know he was arrested, right?
I don't know who he is.
Mr. T.O.N.Y. or a Benjamin Blink?
I don't know who that is and I don't want to really.
I don't care.
You know he was indicted.
You don't know that way that is?
Nope.
You know who it is?
I don't.
Yeah, the guy who copyright struck me. Oh
The one that copyright struck for my song. Yeah, what was he indicted for?
cyberbullying harassment
sending like unwanted materials in people's houses and
Good
See that's real life because that was affecting you in real life. Yeah
So did wow, okay?
Yeah, and so I haven't where can I see the court filings? Do you have that information?
Discord I mean it's like I think I don't think I have that but it was like there was a I just I was sharing that
I think it was in my like my other like bank account
Because hold on one second
But it was out of New Jersey. I could probably find the paper
Or I might have sent it to you and just go already you might want to check
Your oldest might just because I might have my own message something or something. Are you looking at it?
I'm offside having sex
She's jealous
You think you think like
Christopher Farley if he was like a Mexican you look like
You look like a gay
O'Haniel database
He looks like Kathy Bates, actually.
That's what he looks like most of all.
Kathy Bates.
I like to, I don't know if you're coming back.
I'm sorry if I did something wrong.
I mean, it's like, I love you.
It's worth sticking by me.
I know you're sticking by me for awhile.
Here, I'm gonna play some more of this tape.
In conjunction with IRL News Time,
I am your hostess, Alexandra Mayers.
And I, and I'm going to keep this brief.
I decided to go live tonight to share my opinion and my thoughts on a certain live streamer.
I'm here, of course, to discuss a live streamer known as Brandon Kew, who I think...
Has received the forgiveness of the Lord and I think that the time has come for these IP to
affiliated communities to
Grant Brandon Q a new slate very recently a channel that I follow closely has
entered into a little bit of a scandal by allowing Brandon Q to be part of the panel.
I'm of course referring to a live streamer known as the Cult of Psyche,
and I just want to promote the Cult of Psyche as much as possible.
I think that he is an extremely educated, insightful man.
And I think that everyone who is watching this live stream right now
should go ahead and view Cult of Psyche's channel and get to know him.
because I wholeheartedly support him.
And I, like so many others,
watched his live stream with Brandon Q.
And I think that these IP2-affiliated communities
have him all wrong.
I don't think there is any evidence
of Brandon Q being a pedophile.
and anything that you bring my way,
I will wholeheartedly reject it.
Like I said, a cult of psyche entered
into a significant amount of scandal
by having Brandon Q on his panel.
And my thoughts on that are that
cult of psyche is a very good person,
extremely so.
And you know, based on the people that I support,
And I consider myself to be a very good judge of character.
I like, I make sure to throw my weight in my support
behind only the best people.
For instance, I've not made any secret
about how much I support Big T,
AKA Controla, AKA Carissa.
I've been watching many of her live streams where she goes to her reflection journals,
where she reflects on the Word of God. And I wholeheartedly support anyone who is a Christian.
In fact, if you have, in fact, if you want nothing to do with God, I don't really think
that I want to have anything to do with you. That's just my opinion. I'm allowed to have it.
Just like how I'm allowed to have an opinion on Brandon Q. I know that this is going to be a very controversial position
Brandon Q is a young man and he's a young man that likes to enjoy his youth and
maybe others other youths
But I don't think that he's a pedophile
There are many in these communities that are making these allegations and accusations on him and I don't think it is right
to unjustly villainize someone,
especially with something as serious
as an allegation of pedophilia.
You know, I know that I would never falsely accuse
people of pedophilia.
I would never make that kind of claim without proof.
I just think that Brandon Q is being a young,
hetero, Latino male.
And I think it's time for these communities
to give them a second chance.
Of course, I know that there have been people that have been leaving their responses to my opinion.
GANVILLE.
Now, GANVILLE, I want to make something very clear to you.
I have not watched your live streams in quite some time.
I recall watching your live streams long ago in the past.
and I thoroughly enjoyed masturbating to it.
That was a long time ago and I don't really remember
much of the content that you have.
I think that the only reason that you're coming after
Brandon Q is for attention.
I think you're acting out of vanity and greed.
If you want my opinion of Gamble,
I believe that he peaked quite a long time ago.
and now he needs attention for his channel,
not only for validation, but for donations.
And it's really quite sad that you need
to unjustly villainize someone without any proof.
I believe that Ganball has lied extensively on brand and queue.
I don't think he can produce any evidence that Brandon Q is a pedophile.
I believe that Gamble has also levied those accusations on Zaya as well.
I know that Gamble has levied the accusations of pedophilia against Zaya and said that Zaya is a pedophile.
And I am aware that at one point he did express romantic interest with a 16-year-old girl.
and then proceeded to speak to her repeatedly
and then have her come over to his home to live with him.
But I believe that Zaya is in a FIBA file.
Maybe at one point he was in a FIBA file,
but is he a pedophile for speaking
to a 16 year old girl sexually?
No, I don't think it is.
Maybe he was in a FIBA file at one point.
Just like perhaps Brandon Q was in a FIBA file at one point,
but that doesn't mean he was a pedophile.
So, Ganvo, I encourage you to just stay in your lane.
I think that you have an over-inflated sense
of your own opinion,
and ultimately no one really cares about it.
There's somebody else that I must address. I am aware also that Trisha Licious has made a live stream on me
There were a lot of different things that she said that I don't really want to address right now
But one thing that really upset me is when she was bashing me for my Christian faith
I am a deeply devoutly Christian woman. You will find that on my main channel
I have still been conducting my daily reading of the Bible
And I'm deeply insulted when somebody questions it.
So I ask you, Trisha, I have been very supportive of you.
And I've given you all my support on all my live streams.
And I think that you are doing a great job as a mother,
but do not, do not come from my Christian faith.
I myself,
have been a victim of unjustified persecution.
I am a black woman.
And I do believe that Brandon Q is being attacked unjustly.
But really, for anybody who has an opinion
on anything that I have to say,
I just want you to understand that chat is not real to me.
None of you are real.
Your opinion doesn't matter to me.
Do you see, I am goddess level.
I have reached celebrity of heights
that you will not possibly comprehend.
And I have the word of God to back me up.
I have the Lord on my side.
Your opinion doesn't hurt me in any way.
It doesn't faze me.
Most of you, a lot of you are just racist,
just attacking me because I'm a black woman.
You hate all of the opinions that I have,
only specifically because I'm a black woman.
Okay.
I think that this live stream has come to an end.
Brandon Q, by the way, will now be allowed into my panel,
whenever I have an open panel.
Brandon Q was allowed in my chat.
If I've previously blocked Brandon Q, he is now unblocked.
And if you have anything to say about that,
why don't you just go ahead and go to Marshals?
or Michaels, or Home Depot, and just buy a rope.
And then just come find me, and then what you can do
is that you can tie the rope into a noose.
And then you can come find me,
and then just put the noose around my neck,
and you can hang me from a tree.
Because I know that's what a lot of you want to do.
It'll be easy to get away
with murdering a black woman nowadays.
You can get away with it. You can get away with killing me if if you have a problem with my opinion
You can just lynch me
Everyone have a good night
Make sure to read your Bibles thoroughly
Make sure to praise God and remember you are nothing compared to me. Have a good night
Good night, psyche
Good night, Brandon
If you like what you see today,
consider donating to my cash up down below.
Every little bit helps my channel grow.
Thank you so much.
Enjoy.
Very recently, a channel that I follow closely
that I have strong judgment when it comes down to people.
And I consider myself as reading all of her,
where I wholeheartedly support Gaurd.
I wholeheartedly support her purchasing of all these.
And I believe that at a time,
Alex, you are just such a dirty, disgusting bitch.
Fuck you so much.
I can't believe these words
are about to come out of my mouth.
Jesus fucking Christ.
If you like what you see today,
consider donating down below.
Every little bit helps the channel grow.
Thank you so much, enjoy.
Hey.